[? Ric Ocasek: Emotion in Motion]
当我还是个小女孩的时候
[woman] When I was a little girl,
东西分成原价和妈妈价两类
there were real prices and mom prices.
原价是能让你耀眼三周的东西
Real prices got you shiny, sparkly things that lasted three weeks,
而妈妈价是...褐色的东西
and mom prices got you brown things...
可以用一辈子
...that lasted forever.
你留意到这双鞋可是打5折?
You notice they were 50 percent off?
- 看看...
- Look at... - [laughing]
但当我看着商店的橱窗
[woman] But when I looked into shop windows,
我看到了另一个世界
I saw another world.
一个充满完美商品的梦幻世界
A dreamy world full of perfect things.
一个成年女子能拥有一切的世界
A world where grown-up girls got what they wanted.
她们太美了
[woman] They were beautiful.
就像仙女和公主一样
Like fairies or princesses.
她们甚至不需要钱 她们有魔法卡
They didn't even need any money, they had magic cards.
我也想有一张
I wanted one.
小时候我怎么也没想到
Little did I know...
我居然有了12张
...I would end up with 1 2.
[? Adrienne Bailon: Uncontrollable]
Rebecca Bloomwood 职业:记者
[woman] Rebecca Bloomwood. Occupation: Journalist.
外套:Visa卡 连衣裙:AMEX卡
Jacket: Visa. Dress: AMEX.
皮带:MasterCard卡
Belt: MasterCard.
这是古典款式 我还得到1%的现金回馈
It's vintage. And I got one percent cash back.
手袋:Gucci的!
Bag: Gucci!
花多少钱都值得
And worth every penny.
搬到纽约来 我会遇上一些男人
Moving to New York, I met guys.
让我对一切充满期待
And that kind of put things in perspective.
因为当你遇到一帅哥 他对着你笑
'Cause you know that thing, when you see someone cute and he smiles,
你的心就会像
and your heart kind of goes
暖暖的奶油被涂在热吐司上
like warm butter sliding down hot toast?
嗯 这就是我看到商店的感觉
Well, that's what it's like when I see a store.
只是感觉更美妙
Only it's better.
你知道 男人永远不会像
[Rebecca] You see, a man will never love you
商店那样子爱你 款待你
or treat you as well as a store.
要是男人不合适 你也不能7天内退货
If a man doesn't fit, you can't exchange him seven days later
把他换成羊绒毛衣
for a gorgeous cashmere sweater.
商店里的味道总是那么清新
And a store always smells good.
商店总能燃起你的欲望
A store can awaken a lust for things
渴求你不曾知道你需要的东西
you never even knew you needed.
当你的手指抓住那些闪亮的新手袋...
And when your fingers grasp those shiny, new bags...
噢 就是这样!噢 就是这样!
[Rebecca] Oh, yes! Oh, yes!
噢 不...我花了900元
Oh, no... I spent $900.
你负责报道园艺及工具博览会 对吧?
So you are covering the yard and tool expo, right?
交给我好了
- I'm on it. - [phone ringing]
好吧 别惊慌
[Rebecca] OK, don't panic.
冷静 冷静  Bloomingdale's(美国奢侈品连锁店)
Calm. Calm. Bloomingdale's.
嗯 那是裤子
Well, that would be the pants.
我需要那条裤子来衬...
I had to get the pants to match the...
- 噢 鞋子 - 我...
- Oh, shoes. - I...
等一下...
[Rebecca] Hold on...
- 有人偷了我的信用卡! - 噢 天呀
- Somebody's stolen my credit card! - Oh, my God.
有人偷了我的信用卡
Somebody has stolen my credit card and gone
而且在纽约到处乱花钱
on an insane spending spree around New York.
- 不! - 是呀!
- No! - Yeah!
户外世界?我从来没去过户外世界
Outdoor World? I've never been to Outdoor World.
不 你去过
Yes, you have.
- 你买了个帐篷 记得吗? - 不 我没有
- You bought that tent, remember? - No, I didn't.
- 是Kristen的欢送礼物 - 我从没见过帐篷
- For Kristen's going-away present. - Never seen a tent.
我负责筹款 然后把钱给你了
I organized the collection and gave you the money.
噢...
Oh...
"特殊技能: 剑术?" 芬兰语流利?
"Special skills: Fencing"? Fluent in Finnish?
怎么了?谁不美化他们的简历?
[Rebecca] What? Who doesn't pad their resume?
鞋子!谢谢
Shoe! Thanks.
你怎么不在自己的办公室里换衣服?
Why can't you get changed in your own office?
让的每个人都知道
And let everyone at Gardening Today
我秘密地接受杂志的面试?
know I've secretly arranged an interview at Alette magazine?
我提到我要去杂志面试了吗?
Did I mention I have an interview at Alette magazine?
说过好几百次了
Only about a billion times.
- 好吧... - 感觉这变化有点大 对吧?
- OK... - It's kind of a leap, isn't it?
从园艺到时尚?
Gardening to fashion?
我是说 不是说你做不到...
I mean, not that I meant you couldn't do it...
Suze...14岁开始 我就想替杂志工作
Suze... since I was 14 I wanted to work at Alette magazine.
要是我能得到这份工作  我就能永远都开开心心了
If I can just get this job I will be happy forever.
哇
Wow.
[? Kat DeLuna: Calling You]
Rebecca 你才收到900美元的信用卡账单
[Rebecca] Rebecca, you just got a credit card bill of $900.
你不需要围巾了
You do not need a scarf.
是呀...
Then again...
...谁需要围巾?
...who needs a scarf?
在脖子上围条旧牛仔裤 就能保暖了
Wrap some old jeans around your neck, that'll keep you warm.
你妈就会那样
That's what your mother would do.
说得对 她就是这么做的
You're right, she would.
关键是这条围巾
The point about this scarf is that
它会成为你的象征...
it would become part of a definition of your...
你精神的象征
Of your psyche.
你明白我的意思了吗?
Do you see what I mean?
嗯 我明白 继续说
No, I do. Keep talking.
它会让你眼睛看上去更大
It would make your eyes look bigger.
嗯...
Mmm... [sighs]
它会让我的发型看上去更昂贵
It would make my haircut look more expensive.
它配什么都好看
You'd wear it with everything.
这是一项投资
It would be an investment.
这样你面试时会充满自信
You would walk into that interview confident.
- 自信 - 而且泰然自若
- Confident. - And poised.
- 泰然自若 - 那个围绿色围巾的女孩
- Poised. - The girl in the green scarf.
我要这条绿色围巾 谢谢
The green scarf, please.
选得好 这是最后一条了
Good choice. It's the last one.
谢谢你120元 你想怎么付款呢?
That'll be $120. How would you like to pay?
给你50元现金 这张卡刷30元...
Here's $50 in cash, can you put 30 on this card...
这张10元
Ten on that.
这张20元
Twenty on that.
- 它太好看了 - 被拒了
- It's so cute. - Declined.
什么?你能不能... 你能不能再试一次?
Really? Could you just... Could you try it again?
真的被拒了
- [register beeps] - Really declined.
- 你能不能把它放到一边...? - 打折商品无法保留
- Could you put this to one side...? - I can't hold sale items.
- 让一下 紧急情况 - 到后面排队!
- Excuse me. It's an emergency. - [man] Back of the line!
不好意思 这是紧急情况 你让一让 不好意思!
Excuse me, this is an emergency. Excuse you, excuse me!
- 你能兑现吗? - 什么?
- Do you do cash back? - What?
要是我给你一张23元的支票 你能不能给我
If I give you a check for $23, will you give me
一个热狗和20块现金 拜托你了?
one of your hot dogs and $20 cash back, please?
- 我看上去像银行吗? - 我待会有个面试
- Do I look like a bank? - I have an interview.
但他们不能保留打折商品 那是条极重要的围巾
They don't hold items. It's a desperately important scarf.
极重要的围巾
Desperately important scarf.
你知道吧? 是送给我婶祖母 她住院了
Know what? It's for my great-aunt. She's in the hospital.
你不能让医院把暖气温度调高吗?
Can you ask them to turn the heating up?
需要加芥末吗?
Want mustard with that?
求求你了 我买下你所有的热狗
Please. I will buy all of your hot dogs.
- 你97个热狗都买了? - 成交
- You'll take 97 hot dogs? - Done.
我要怎么...
Who do I make it...
你这是花了23元买一个热狗!
That means you just paid $23 for a hot dog!
你想要你的围巾 我想要我的热狗
You want your scarf, I want my hot dog.
价格和价值不是一回事
Cost and worth are very different things.
谢谢你!我婶祖母会很感谢你的
Thank you! My aunt will really appreciate it.
- Hi. - 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
我是来杂志面试的
I'm here for the interview at Alette magazine.
...噢 满了  昨天说内部招到人了
Alette... Oh, filled, internally. Yesterday.
他们在网页贴了出来 让我看看 是谁得到了这份工作?
They did post it on the Web. Let's see, who got the job?
噢...说曹操曹操到
Oh... Speak of the devil.
[? The Pussycat Dolls: Bad Girl]
Alicia... Billington.
她有着世界上最长的双腿
She has the longest legs in the world.
她心里一清二楚
She notes resentfully.
好极了 包都出问题了
Great. [sighs] Faulty.
- 围巾很不错 - 谢谢 我为了面试买的
- Nice scarf. - Thanks. I bought it for the interview.
等一下...过来
Scusi... [whispering] Come on.
这会儿 正好有个面试
As we speak, interviews are being held
在
at Successful Saving.
- 金融杂志? - 不要小看它 孩子
- The money magazine? - Snort not, sweet child.
也许才是你的翡翠城 (翡翠城:的场景)
Alette may be your Emerald City,
但是可以成为你的踏脚石
but Successful Saving could be your yellow-brick road.
Dantay-West是像大家庭一样的出版集团
Dantay-West is a family of magazines that acts like a family.
非常偏袒内部人才
Deeply nepotistic. Ugh.
我给你的意见是 亲爱的桃乐西 (桃乐西:女主角)
So my advice to you, dear Dorothy,
所以...一旦加入了...就是自家人了
is thus... Once you're in... you're in.
我加入
I'm in.
你好
- [phone ringing] - [woman] Hello, Successful Saving.
[inhaling]
Bloodwood小姐?
Ms. Bloomwood?
这个面试是什么形式的?
So what form does this interview take?
是概况的了解 兴趣什么的...
Is it just mainly a general chat, hobbies...
噢 不 不 不 就是专门谈论金融方面的
Oh, no, no, no. It's very specific on finance.
投Y的蝴蝶效应 期货 之类的东西
Butterfly investments, futures. That sort of thing.
- 但是它值12亿元... - 祝你好运
- But he's worth 1 .2 billion... - Good luck.
- 谢谢 - 我们谈了那么久 一点用也没有
- Thanks. - We talked and talked. Said nothing.
对 当然了 他明白规则是怎样的
Yeah, of course I did. He understands the rules.
它总是...当然我们能拿到钱
It's always... Of course we got the bill.
听着 我得挂了 我得面试
Listen, I've got to go. I'm interviewing.
嗯 对 不 不是我...再见
Mm-mm. Yeah, no, not me... Bye.
抱歉 好了 嗯 Rebecca...
Sorry about that. Right, um, Rebecca...
- 噢!我们见过面了! - 嗨!我们见过了 谢谢你
- Ah! We met! - Hi! We did. Thank you.
生病的婶婶 围巾 对吧 你把围巾给她了吗?
Sick aunt, scarf. Yep. Did you get it to her?
给了 一个陌生人像你那么友善 实在是...
I did. And when a stranger is kind like that, it's just...
- 哇 - 那很好 嗯...
- Wow. - That's lovely. Um...
- 你带简历来了吗? - 我带了 嗯 我带来!
- Do you have a resume for me? - I do. Yes, I do!
嗯...
Ah... [grunting]
我...告诉你也一样吧
I... could pretty much just tell you.
我名字叫Rebecca Bloomwood
My name is Rebecca Bloomwood,
我做记者已经五年了
I've been a journalist for five years.
我对篡改数字非常在行
I'm very comfortable juggling numbers,
我会说流利的芬兰语 我知道...
I speak fluent Finnish, I know...
- 芬兰语? - 对 芬兰语
- Finnish? - Yes, Finnish.
- 我也... - 这很有趣 你怎么会芬兰语?
- I'm also... - That's interesting. Why Finnish?
你后面的是什么?
What's behind you?
- 嗯 - 噢 天呀
- Um... - [panting] Oh, my God.
噢 是个赤裸的男人 很抱歉
Oh, it's a naked man. Oh, sorry.
我吓到了 我...
It gave me such a fright. I, uh...
我不知道那是什么 显然他头被砍了
I didn't know what it was. Clearly, he's beheaded.
是谁这么做的?
Who would do that to him?
嗯 我有几个问题
[clears throat] Well, a few questions.
但是 看呀!会让你想知道
But, look! Makes you wonder
5楼的人会看到啥 对吧?
what they're looking at on the fifth floor, right?
你可以把桌子转过去 就能整天对着他
You could turn your desk around and just stare at it all day.
我就...
I would. [laughing]
- 不会 - Bloodwood小姐
- Not. - Ms. Bloomwood.
我不是变态的
I'm not a pervert.
坐下来
Sit down.
我很抱歉 我面试太糟糕了
I'm sorry, I'm terrible at interviews.
你最近都关注哪些金融事件?
Any financial stories that have caught your eye recently?
嗯 我很高兴你这么问
Yes. And I am glad that you brought that up.
因为我很愤怒 是的 说真的
Because I am furious. No, I really am.
我是说 最近的鱼类危机是怎么回事?
No, I mean, what is the story with the recent fish crisis?
鱼类危机?
Fish crisis?
- 国库...危机 - 国库危机
- Fiscal... crisis. - Fiscal crisis.
- 太可怕了 国库的 我是说 - 为什么呢?
- Terrifying. Fiscally, I mean. - How so?
- 因为在国库里 - 对不起
- For the fiscal family. - I'm sorry.
- 没关系 - Bloodwood小姐 你的围巾掉了
- Not a moment too soon. - Ms. Bloomwood, you dropped your scarf.
她死了
She died.
噢 Bloodwood小姐  刚才的25分钟可真难熬啊
Oh, Ms. Bloomwood, you have had a very, very tough 25 minutes.
很高兴你明白!很多人就是...对
I'm glad you understand! So many people just... Right.
好吧 我想我们可以缩短...
OK, so I would propose we curtail...
你是不是把我名字划掉了?
Did you just scrub my name off?
- 噢 不 惯例而已 - 这太过早了吧
- Oh, no. Routine. - That seems premature.
好吧 我提议我们马上结束这次面试
OK, I'm gonna propose that we curtail this interview forthwith.
我会离开 留下你和你的数字
So I'll leave you and your numbers,
但是谢谢你见我
but thank you very much for seeing me,
我很感激...噢!
and I appreciate... Oh!
我很感激一切 祝你顺利
[groaning] I appreciate everything. Good day.
祝你顺利
Good day.
别这样 让我们把帐篷给Great太太吧
Come on. Let's go give Mrs. Great Outdoors her tent.
她不是退休
[sobbing] She's not retiring.
- 什么? - 她是离弃一艘沉船
- What? - She's abandoning a sinking ship.
那个卑鄙小人! 杂志社要倒闭了 她知道的!
That little rat! The magazine's folding and she knew!
她知道 但是她不告诉我们
She knew and she didn't tell anybody.
嗯 从好的方面来看 你讨厌在那工作呀
Well, on the bright side, you hated working for that magazine.
那是我的收入来源 Suze 我需要收入!
[sighing] It was my income, Suze. I need my income!
好吧 Bex 最重要的是别惊慌
OK, Bex, the most important thing is not to panic.
[phone ringing]
- 别接电话! - 不!
- [Suze] Don't answer the phone! - [both] No!
- 也许是债务人! - 你好?
- It might be a debt collector! - Hello?
- 是Derek Smeath - 列表 把列表拿来!
- It's Derek Smeath. - The list. Get the list!
- 我想我看到它在那里 - 拿着这台灯
- I think I saw it over here. - Take the lamp!
- 在这里! - BIoomingdaIe's连锁店...
- It's here! - Bloomingdale's...
- 去医院治疗抑郁 - 因工作滞留在芬兰
- Hospital for depression. - Detained in Finland on work.
Visa那废物
Visa, dead dog.
城市债务追讨公司 你来说
All City Debt Collection. You have to do it.
- 你好! 嗨! - Bloodwood小姐?
- Hello! Hi! - [Derek] Ms. Bloomwood?
- 你好 - 很抱歉 我不是她
- Hello. - I'm sorry. It's actually not.
她还在恢复...你知道...好吧
She's still recovering from... You know... OK.
我会让她尽快打给你
I'll have her call you as soon as...
- 对 - 只要她一回来
- Yes? - As soon as she's come back
- 从...从... - 芬兰!芬兰!
- from... From... - Finland! Finland!
- 显然她还没有... - 呃!
- Clearly she's not too... - Aah!
[phone clatters]
怎么你那么多借口都和芬兰有关?
Why do so many of your excuses involve Finland?
因为没有人会去芬兰查 Tarkie
'Cause no one checks up on Finland, Tarkie.
现在我怎么付你房租呢?
How am I going to pay you the rent now?
嗯 我马上把你的房租支票撕掉!
Well, I'm ripping up your rent check!
不 Suze 你不能再这么做了
No, Suze, you can't do it again.
这是我的公寓 嗯 其实是我父母的
It's my apartment, well, my parent's apartment,
- 但是规矩是我定的 - 我要给你买一份最大的礼物
- but it's my rules. - I'm gonna buy you the biggest present.
是的!我知道去哪儿最好 梅西百货正在大减价!
I am! I know where I'm going to go. There's a sale at Macy's!
Tarkie...
我会在我家里的
I'll be at my place.
谢谢你 宝贝 Bex 我去拿龙舌兰酒 你去拿账单
Thanks, baby. Bex, I'll get the tequila, you get the bills.
我来吧 不会那么糟的
I'll do this. It can't be that bad.
这就像是撕创可贴 会没事的
It's just like a Band-Aid. It's gonna be fine.
[both gasping loudly]
Bex!你在Marc Jacobs 花了2百美元买内衣?
Bex! Two hundred dollars on Marc Jacobs underwear?
噢 内衣是基本人权呀
Oh, underwear is a basic human right.
薰衣草蜜花了78元!
Seventy-eight dollars on lavender honey!
我替商店助理感到抱歉  她眼神太懒散了
I felt sorry for the shop assistant. She had a lazy eye.
我不知道她在看哪个方向  太糟糕了
I didn't know which way she was looking. It was so sad.
这个我都不想开口了
I can't even talk about this one.
脚部水疗?你去哪里干嘛?
A foot spa? What were you doing at a foot spa?
我们休息一下吧
Let's take a break.
他们说我是非常重要的客人
They said I was a valued customer.
现在他们给我寄威胁信了
Now they send me hate mail.
Bex
- [adding machine rattling] - [Suze] Bex.
噢 天呀...
Oh, God...
你怎么能还得了16262.70元?
How are you going to pay off sixteen thousand twelve hundred
而且你连工作都没有了?
and 62 dollars and 70 cents with no job?
我可以中彩票
I could win the lottery.
也许你该有个B计划
Maybe you should have a backup plan.
噢! B计划 我想到了 我想到了 B计划
Oh! Backup plan, I got it, I got it. Backup plan.
好吧 当Tarkie想到他梦想的工作
OK. When Tarkie thought of his dream job,
他会写个自己的计划 你知道吧
he, um, wrote this proposal just about him, you know,
写写他真实的自我 你也可以啊
what he's made of and that's what you can do.
你可以写篇时尚文稿 寄到
You can write a fashion piece and send it to Alette.
就像说"嘿  看看我能做什么!"
Like, "Hey, Alette, look what I can do!"
你只需要想想写点什么
You just gotta figure out what to write about.
"把你的鞋子当作是一项投资
"Consider your shoe an investment.
一切都取决于它
Everything is resting upon it.
最重要的是每一双鞋子
The most important point is that every shoe
都应该赢得你的..."
should earn its place in your..."
Bex 这太有趣了 你太聪明了
Bex, this is so funny. You're so smart.
- 你是史上最好的作者! - 你喜欢吗?
- You're the best writer ever! - Do you like it?
- 你太难以置信了! - 等一下!再写一封
- You're fabulous! - Wait! Another one.
给那个不请我的男人
To that guy at that savings thingy magazine who didn't hire me.
[laughing]
"亲爱的拮据编辑...
"Dear Uptight Editor...
- 那份工作你留着放屁吧" - 骑单车的男人!
- You can stick yourjob up your ass." - Man on a bike!
你好!
Hello!
"这里有20元 给自己买点得体的衣服吧"
"Here's $20. Buy yourself some decent clothes."
我回来了!
I'm back!
噢 天呀 噢 天呀
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
这是给杂志的
This is for Alette magazine.
拜托了 拜托了亲吻它 祈求好运
Please, please. Kiss it for good luck.
- 还有这个...
- Mwah! - And this one...
...是给成功理财先生的
...is for Mr. Successful Saving.
恶...钱 钱 钱
Bleah... Money, money, money.
我最好得到那份工作 我没有钱了
I better get the job, I've got no money.
我没有钱了
[sobbing] I've got no money.
* 你把石灰撒到椰子上... *
? You put the lime in the coconut...
这不令你高兴吗?
Doesn't this just cheer you up?
- 没效果 妈妈 - 别这样 你会得到另一份工作的
- It's not working, Mom. - Come on, you'll get anotherjob.
生活就像旧物交换会 你永远不知道
Life is like a swap meet. You never know
财富的出现...
when great riches...
通常是不可预料的
...are going to turn up unexpectedly.
25美分能买些什么?
What can I get for a quarter?
这个!
This!
- 是吗? - 好看极了
- Comme ?a? - It's fantastic.
[? Gwen Stefani: Rich Girl on cell phone]
- 那个要多少钱? - 越看越喜欢
- What are they gettin' for that? - It's growing on me.
- 这个多少钱? - 20元
- How much for this? - Twenty dollars.
- 噢! - 你好?
- Oh! - ?Hola?
Rebecca 我是的Luke Brandon
Um, Rebecca. Luke Brandon, Successful Saving.
你好?
Yes?
抱歉那么早打给你  但是我收到你的信件了
Sorry to call so early, but I got your letter.
我得说我有点惊讶
And I have to say it was a bit of a surprise.
嗯 我希望我表明了我的观点
Well, I hope I made my point.
哦 确实 你写得十分清楚
Oh, you did. You did. Very well.
尤其是隐喻部分 非常机智
The whole metaphor. Very clever.
那可不 对吧  这个比隐喻简直是...
Yes, wasn't it. The whole metaphor was...
等等... 什么? 抱歉没听清...
Wait... What? I'm sorry...
形容证券投资的准则
Describing the principles of security investment
从不同女性选择鞋子的角度入手
in terms of the way different women purchase different shoes
真是很... 别出心裁
was... different.
喂? 听着你那边很嘈杂啊
Hello? Sounds like you might be in the middle of something.
我要说的是这让我突然有个想法
I was trying to say that it gave me an idea.
你想加入我们吗? 我并不是...
[clears throat] Would you like to come in? I don't...
宝贝 有什么想买的吗?
Can I help you, dear?
我刚给Alette杂志社的编辑寄了20美元
I think I just sent the editor ofAlette magazine $20
来买点体面的衣服 保住饭碗
to buy herself decent clothes and stick herjob up her ass.
[elevator bell dings]
[grunting]
- [gasps] - [indistinct chattering]
这些是给...
- These go... - [elevator bell dings]
- 嘿 AIette需要的衣服 - 我会打给她的助理的
- Hey, clothes for Alette. - [woman] I'll call her assistant.
嘿 衣服先放这儿等待AIette挑选
Hi. Clothes are here for Alette's approval.
她一会出来
She'll be right out.
周五晚上跟我出去约会怎样?
What do you think about you and me going out on Friday night?
- 哦... - 我是说 如果你愿意的话
- Ooh... - I mean, if you want to.
你周五晚想出去吗?
Would you like to go out on Friday night?
我还不知道呢 可能会有计划吧
I don't know. I might have plans.
你可以... 你有穿过这里的衣服吗?
You might... Do you ever wear any of this stuff?
有些对我来说不太合适
Some of it's a little far out for me.
- 太不合适了  - 没错
- Totally far out. - Yeah.
太疯狂了 我想这就是时尚吧?
It's crazy, but I guess that's the world of high fashion?
- 没错 - 对 我知道的
- [chuckles] Yes. - Yeah, I know about that.
我做得很好 不会失职的
I am one of the best. I don't let this out of my sight.
我用生命来保护这些东西
I guard it with my life.
我压力很大啊
A lot of pressure on me
要确保信送到每个人手上...
to make sure everyone gets these letters...
- 准时送达  - 必须要完成我的工作
- Get them there on time. - Got to get my job done.
瞧 我严谨得对待我的工作
See, I take my job very seriously.
- 没错 要投递... - 哦 真的?
- Yes. And to deliver... - Oh, really?
要投递信件 作为一个邮递员
And to deliver the mail, but as the mail carrier
把信送到大家手上对我来说压力很大
it's a lot of pressure on me to get people their letters,
我从没弄丢过一封信
I've never lost a letter yet.
我再也不想看到竖排扣眼的设计了
[French accent] I want no more vertical buttonholes.
我烦死这种设计了
I'm so bored with vertical buttonholes.
这是给Paolo拍摄"万花筒"主题的衣服吗?
Is this for the Kaleidoscope shoot with Paolo?
哦 这件不要!
[speaking French] Oh, but this!
Cavalli 他太了解我了
[gasps] Cavalli. He has read my mind.
太棒了 这些衣服都可以用
It's marvelous. We can use it all.
推进去
Take it in.
哦 天啊 你怎么在这儿?
[Alicia gasps] Oh, God. What are you doing?
这是Alette杂志社 这是你该来的地方吗?
This is Alette. Is this where you should be?
哦 对 哦 对
Oh, yes. Oh, yes.
Dantay West并不仅仅是 邀我来出任这本杂志的编辑
Dantay-West didn't hire me to be an editor of this magazine.
他们希望我拯救它脱离泥沼
They hired me to throw it a rope and pull it out of the swamp.
这就是...
- [knocking on glass] - And that's...
大家好 我是Rebecca BIoomwood
Hi, everyone. I'm Rebecca Bloomwood.
坐下 Rebecca
Sit down, Rebecca.
是什么使得一本杂志在报刊亭中脱颖而出?
What makes a magazine move from the newsstands?
[chair squeaking]
是真实的 质朴的故事
Real, unvarnished stories,
这在于我们描写的人物是否逼真
whether the people that we are writing about like them or not.
成功理财杂志现在是 财经报业中的"人物杂志"
Successful Saving is currently the People magazine
这也是终极目标
of financial journalism, and this is where that ends.
从今天起...
- From now... - [pencil sharpener grinding]
对不起
Sorry.
从今天起 我们不再模仿 我们去试验
From now on we don't copy, we examine.
- 我们去调查 - 哦!
- We probe. - Ooh!
我喜欢你那篇稿子 我电话里提过了
I liked your piece. I said that on the phone.
- 好 好  - HayIey!
- Good. Good. - Hayley!
来三周的实习期怎么样
What do you say a three-week trial.
- 给她这张办公桌  - 哦 真不错啊
- And give her this cubicle. - Oh, this one's lovely.
这桌子都是3*6米规格的
They're all three by six.
你可以先写一篇关于利率变化
You can start with a thousand words on the effect of changing
对信用卡的年利率的影响 一千字
interest rate on store card APRs.
好的
Good.
你的眼镜上还挂着标签呢
[whispers] You still have the label on your new glasses.
什么? 哦
What? Oh.
你在理财财经杂志上班? 你?
You took a job at a savings magazine? You?
我也知道听着挺怪的 但确实如此 已成事实
I know it sounds bad, but it is, in fact,
像是规划得很好的计划的一部分
part of a very structured plan.
没错 这很棒 但从很多方面来说
Yeah, that's great, but then in a lot of ways
也不见得是个美差 那句话怎么说来着?
it's kinda not great. What do they call it
就像是动物保护协会的人 被头牛踩死的时候?
when an animal rights person gets trampled to death by a cow?
没有这种说法吧
I don't think there is a word for that.
''讽刺''  对于Rebecca BIoomwood来说
"Ironic." Ironic that Rebecca Bloomwood
她要教大家如何理财 真是讽刺
is advising people on how to handle money.
但我觉得这也不错
But I guess it would be nice
如果我的伴娘能买得起自己的裙子
if my maid of honor could afford her own dress.
- 他求婚了? - 对!
- He asked? - Yes!
哦 天啊! 你真该也在那儿的
Oh, my God! You should've been there.
- 他怎么说的? - 嘿!
- How did he say it? - [man] Hey!
你的卡达到信用额度极限了
The, uh, credit limit on your card was reached.
我希望我未来老公 能在巴尼斯纽约精品店跟我求婚
You know, I think I want my husband- to-be to propose to me in Barneys.
- 你在干嘛? - 没啥
- What are you doing? - Nothing.
- 不 你有干啥  - 我给你找到这本最适合你的书
- [girl] Yes, you are. - I just found the perfect book for you.
控制你的购物欲 由Garrett E. Barton主讲
Control Your Urge to Shop, with Garrett E. Barton.
就是敝人
That's me.
最近你是否发现自己沉迷于商场购物?
Do you find yourself constantly drawn toward stores?
- 对 - 没有
- Yes. - Nope.
看到新款商品你是否心跳加速
Does your heart quicken when you see new merchandise
整齐的叠堆起来的商品?
in neatly stacked piles?
- 对! 这人说得没错  - 不
- Yes! This guy's good. - No.
对这些问题你是否回答"不" 也在抵制?
Did you answer no to these questions and are consequently in denial?
- 是的 - 不!
- Yes. - No!
你是不是又答了''不''?
Did you just say "no" again?
- 不 - 是的
- No. - [both] Yes.
第一步: 清理你的生活 统统丢弃
Step one: de-clutter your life. Throw it all out.
装起来 丢了!
Just box it up and toss it!
简洁有序将是你的新口号
Simplicity and order are your new watchwords.
抱歉 你好?
- [phone rings] - Excuse me. Hello?
这个来电呼唤着新的开始
- [grunts] - It's a fresh start calling.
你的新开始
And it's for you.
[creaking]
在你上班途中
[Garrett] On your way to work,
忽视那些橱窗里发来的诱惑之声
ignore the siren call of the store window.
你的新祷告文是 ''我需要这个吗?''
Your new mantra is, "Do I need this?"
不要
No.
这是什么?
What's this?
关于信用卡年利率的一千字稿件?
A thousand words on store card APRs?
看着像是从"傻瓜理财"书上直接抄下来的
Which looks as if it's been copied straight out of Money for Dummies.
不 我要的是你从某个角度 来写信用卡的年利率变化
No, I wanted a thousand words on APRs from an angle.
这不就是一个角度吗?
Is that not an angle?
除非你把''平板陈述''也称之为角度
Not unless you call "head-on" an angle.
- 不 我没有  - 重写
- No, I don't. - Try it again.
- 就当提醒我为啥要雇用你  - 好的
- Remind me why I hired you. - OK.
Rebecca?
- Rebecca? - [yelps]
你刚刚是否拿谷歌搜 ''写年利率的好角度''?
Did you just type "good angles on APRs" into Google?
是的 我拿谷歌搜了
Yes. I Googled.
- 我被炒了? - 拿起你的外套
- Am I fired? - Get your coat.
你认识这些人 对吧?
You know these guys, right?
Comintex ? 通信公司?
Comintex? Communications company?
是的 当然
Yes. Absolutely.
今年对于整个通信业来说
This year has been a year of unparalleled growth
经历了空前的发展
in the communications industry.
总体来说 伙计 你们公司可不是这样的
Overall, pal. Not in your company.
对于我们Comintex公司而言
For us, at Comintex,
利润反映出今年公司所得
profits reflect that this has been a year of acquisitions,
对于APL以及荷兰的光线公司Zandak都是一样的
both of APL and of the Dutch fiber-optic company, Zandak.
巧妙的掩盖了发放的2千4百万的奖金
Neatly masking the 24 million in bonuses
- 他们发给自己 -  可不是嘛
- these guys paid themselves. - Hmph. I know.
现在 我们所需做的 Rebecca  在这种情况下就是需要有人
Now, what we have here, Rebecca, is a situation in which someone
去提一些刁难的问题
needs to be asking some very hard questions.
- 必须的 - 快举手
- Absolutely. - Put your hand up.
- 什么? 不要! - 快举手
- What? No! - Put your hand up.
我可没啥刁钻的问题可问的
I don't have hard-hitting questions.
- 我告诉你几个问题 - 我还是做笔记吧
- I'll give you questions. - I'm gonna take notes.
- 不 快举手  - 我不过是个新手而已
- No, Put your hand up. - I'm more of a student.
你没问题的 快举手
You'll be fine. Put your hand up.
哈罗 你好 哈罗
Hello. Hi. Hello.
- 他没听见 他听不见 - 大声点 站起来
- He's not listening. He can't hear me. - Louder. Stand up.
- Rebecca BIoomwood! - ...应该会看到一个...
- Rebecca Bloomwood! - ...should see a...
你好
- Hello. - [indistinct chattering]
- 我是 我是 我是 - 你好 我是"成功理财"的记者
- From. From. From. From. - Hi, from Successful Saving.
这是本杂志
It's a magazine.
在报告结束后 我们会有提问环节
We'll be taking questions after the report.
好的 ...
Good. Uh...
- 问他 他的薪水是多少 - 你烧伤多少?
- Ask him how much he earns. - How much do you burn?
- 薪水 - 薪水
- Earn. - Earn.
- 抱歉? - 大声点
- Excuse me? - Louder.
你的薪水是多少?
What do you earn?
- 我们稍后才能进行提问 - 为何要给自己发奖金...
- We'll take questions after. - Why award themselves bonuses...
为何给你们自己发奖金...
Why did you award yourself bonuses...
- ...2千4百万... - ...2千3...
- ...twenty-four million... - ...of 23...
- 2千 4百万 - ...亿...
- Twenty-four. Million. - ...billion...
- 百万美元... - 尤其是当投资者损失8%资产的时候
- Million dollars... - ...while investors lost eight percent?
尤其是当投资者损失8%资产的时候
...while your investors lost eight percent?
[gasps, indistinct chattering]
正如我说过的 我很乐意回答提问...
As I said, I'll be happy to answer questions...
这是真的吗?
Is that true?
长时间的犹豫 没有给出答案
A long pause and no answer.
- 长时间的犹豫 没有给出答案  - 不 不...
- Long pause, no answer. - No, no...
你知道我们为什么要这么做吗?
OK. You know why we did that?
像是种残酷的成年礼?
Some kind of cruel initiation rite?
听听这个
Listen to this.
''对于不同的人而言 证券的意义是不同的
"Security can mean different things to different people.
对于某些人  这就像是穿着合适的鞋子去参加派对
For some, it's going to a party wearing the right shoes.
这让你整晚都有安全感
This might leave you feeling secure for an evening,
却会让你后半生有坡脚的危险''
but have a crippling effect on you in later life."
- 我写的  - 是你写的
- I wrote that. - You wrote that.
现在 像Comintex这种公司
Now, what firms like Comintex
它们的虚假繁荣是建立在群众无知上的
thrive on is an endemic lack of public understanding.
它们瞒天过海是因为...
They get away with murder because...
Maisie爱喝汽水 投资了200美元
Maisie with a root beer and a $200 investment portfolio,
她能知道什么呢?
what does she know?
她怎么才能知道那些人真正干了什么呢?
What does she actually know about what those guys are doing?
在于别人告诉她情况
What she's told.
如果她寻找答案的杂志
And if the magazines she looks to for answers
不能很犀利地提出问题
aren't asking the right questions,
这对于Maisie来说不是一本好杂志
it isn't good for Maisie.
我希望你能用一种Maisie 也能明白的方式来阐释真相
I want you to tell the truth in a way that Maisie can understand.
现在回家去吧 给我写一份初步的概要
Now, go home, write me an initial outline
3点之前发邮件给我 好吧?
and e-mail it to me by 3:00. OK?
哦 不
Oh, no.
哦 耶 很好!
Oh, yeah. Nice!
我刚接到Comintex公司的Jeff Kanter的电话
You know, I just got a call from Jeff Kanter at Comintex.
他们在开股东大会
They're having their stockholders' meeting.
- 对 我派人去了  - 没错 你是派人去了
- Yes, I sent someone. - Yeah, you did.
我眼光独到啊 真的 我派去的那个女孩儿
A real find, actually, the girl I sent.
她很犀利 诚恳
She's sparky, honest.
正是我寻找的类型
Exactly the type that I was hoping to find.
我想这就是为什么 Edgar West让你雇用我的原因
I assume that's why Edgar West got you to recruit me.
- 该死! - 哦 右曲球啊
- Damn it! - Ooh. Slice.
我雇用你来保住杂志生存的底线
I hired you to fix the bottom line of this magazine,
我们知道关键就在于广告的收入
and we know the key to that is advertising revenue.
现在 你雇用我是要创造和销售一种产品
Now, you hired me to create a product that sells,
- 而不是单单去卖旧产品 - 如果我倒向Edgar West这边呢
- not to sell a product. - What if I'm with Edgar West.
我们一起打高尔夫 他刚冷淡地跟我说
We're playing golf, and he just turns to me, sort of nonchalantly, and says,
''嘿 我想知道为什么 Luke Brandon会决定雇用
"Hey, I'd like to know why Luke Brandon decided to hire
一个会损害Dantay-West商业利益的记者''
a journalist who could damage the commercial interests of Dantay-West."
- 你感觉如何? - 我不会的 她也不会这样做的
- What do you think about that? - I haven't, because she won't.
[? Lady GaGa: Fashion]
[all chattering]
我觉得自己是在马拉松赛跑
[woman] I feel like I've run a marathon.
他们卖加利亚诺!
[woman 2] They have Galliano!
他们的Gucci对折  CK对折!
They have Gucci half off, Calvin Klein half off!
会轮到你的 耐心等着吧
You'll get your turn, just be patient.
每一次我都问自己''我需要这个吗?''
[Rebecca] At every point I will ask, "Do I need this?"
这边是新入场通道!
There's another entrance this way!
[all screaming]
[? Jordyn Taylor: Accessory]
哇 我需要这个羊绒手套
[Rebecca] Well, these cashmere gloves I need
因为这是冬天 而我长有一双手
as it is winter and I have... hands.
这就是原因
So that's all.
我只卖这个和这个
I'll buy these and these alone.
天啊 米索尼!
[woman] My gosh, Missoni!
现在就离开 坚定且节俭
[Rebecca] Now walk away, strong and frugal.
哦 天啊! 璞琪的靴子
[gasps] Oh, my God! Pucci boots.
降价50%?
Fifty percent off?
我需要买这个吗?
Do I need these?
我需要买这个吗?我需要买这个吗?
[grunting] Do I need these? [gasping] Do I need these?
不
No.
Jeannie , 璞琪的靴子!
Jeannie, Pucci boots!
哦 很抱歉 我先抢到的
Uh, oh, I'm so sorry. I had 'em first.
但你放下来了
But you put them down.
不 我知道我放下了 但是是我先看到的 所以我要买
No, I know I did, but I saw 'em first, so I'm gonna take 'em.
但是你把它们放下了
Then you took your hands off them.
把靴子给我 免得有人要受伤!
Give me the boots, and no one gets hurt!
把靴子给我 把靴子给我!
Give me the boots. Give me the boots!
看! Burberry搞特价啦!
Look! There's a sale on Burberry!
这是最老套的骗术了!
[gasps] That's the oldest trick in the book!
- 给我! - 你竟敢...
- Give 'em! - Don't you tell me...
把靴子给我!
Give me the boots!
我排了一早上的队就为了这个!
I waited in line all morning for this!
啊! 哈哈!
- [grunting] - Ah! Ha-ha!
[? Natasha Bedingfield: Again]
''你的信用卡就像是一件对折的羊绒大衣
[Rebecca] "Your store card is like a 50 percent-off cashmere coat.
初次相见时
The first time you meet,
它发誓会成为你最好的伴侣
it promises to be your best friend.
直到你看仔细  才意识到它其实不是纯羊绒的''
Until you look closely and realize it's not real cashmere."
你被骗了
You've been ripped off.
对 你听明白了? 你听明白了
Right. You get it? You get it.
- 我们都听明白了 现在你走吧  - 哈!
- We get it. Now go away. - Ha!
''然后 冬天来临 你发现那件大衣
[Luke] "Then, as winter comes, you discover that your coat
根本不是你的朋友
isn't actually a friend at all.
你应该看看衣服的细则说明
You should have read the fine print.
应该仔细看清楚 自己要买的是什么东西''
Should look more closely what you're getting into."
你该放张相片进去
You should put a picture in that.
这是个礼物 还没来得及放照片进去呢
It's a present. Haven't got 'round to filling it yet.
我妈从打折店里给我买过一个一样的
My mom bought me this exact one from a thrift store.
可能只是你这个价格的一半
Probably paid half what you paid,
不是说他们经常逛打折店
not that they often shop at thrift stores.
- 怎么了? - 写的很好
- What? - This is good.
- 真的? -
- Really? - Mmm.
是Rebecca BIoomwood写的?
Is it by Rebecca Bloomwood?
当然! 我的朋友Suze亲眼看见我写的
Yes! My friend Suze saw me writing it.
我是说 你想用这个名字发表吗?
[chuckles] I mean, is that how you want your name to appear?
- ''作者 Rebecca BIoomwood''? - 哦 好吧
- "By Rebecca Bloomwood"? - Oh, right.
我不想跟这份杂志有太多关联
I don't want to be too associated with this magazine.
你说什么?
Sorry?
我想这样更好
Because I just think it would be better
做个无名小卒胜过于名人
to be slightly more of an everyman.
就是一点神秘兮兮
Um, a little more ooh-ooh-ohh.
神秘 而不是... Becky?
Mysterious, rather than just... Becky? Hmm.
Hmm.
''戴绿色围巾的女孩  谢谢
"The Girl in the Green Scarf. Thank you.
今早我买了你的杂志
I bought your magazine this morning and have already
并且告知三家商场 如何死守它们的信用卡''
told three stores where to stick their credit cards."
哦! 嘿 来看看
Oh! Hey, check it out:
皇后区的Jay Brogan写来邮件说:
Jay Brogan, Queens, via e-mail:
''天啊 很容易就以为这些人是为你好
"Man, is it easy to feel those guys do it for your benefit.
- 你从未查过年利率'' - 去我那打电话给他吧
- You never check the APR." - Call him from my desk
- 如果你愿意的话  - 不 不 我很好
- if you want. Oh. - No, no. I'm OK.
''我跟你们说 我现在这样做了 谢谢你 绿围巾女士''
"I'll tell you what, I have now. Thanks, Mrs. Green Scarf."
我们从未得到这种反馈
We never get this kind of response.
抱歉 先生  Edgar West的电话
- [knocking on glass] - Excuse me, sir. Edgar West.
这下遭了 他讨厌我们
That's not good. He hates us.
Luke Brandon
Luke Brandon.
我刚花了几分钟时间 好好研究了下
I've just spent a few minutes rather wrapped up
你们 ''绿围巾小姐''的文章
in your "Green Scarf."
我很喜欢
I like it.
显然她对个人理财方面很有热情
Uh, she obviously has a passion for personal finance.
抱歉 但他真的很坚持
Excuse me, I'm sorry, but he is really being persistent.
他非得和你谈谈
He needs to talk to you.
能否跟他说我很忙 谢谢啦
Could you tell him that I'm busy, please.
你很幸运  Brandon先生
You're a lucky man, Mr. Brandon.
我的这个慈善基金会的主席...
It's this charity that I'm the chairperson of, it's...
谢谢您 先生 看来他很喜欢这个专栏啊
Thank you, sir. It seems that he liked the column so much
还把杂志复印件给他的孩子看了
that he's sending extra copies of the magazine to his children.
哦 天啊 我真不敢相信
Oh, my God. I can't believe that.
[applause]
我真的很抱歉 先生 2号线有个男士打电话来
I'm really sorry, sir. There's a man holding on line two,
他说事关生死
and he says it's a matter of life or death.
- 他叫什么名字? -  Derek Smeath
- What's his name? - Um, Derek Smeath.
- Derek Smeath - 哦! 不!
- Derek Smeath. - Oh! No!
哈!
Ha!
这个前男友缠着你多久了?
Exactly how long has this ex-boyfriend been stalking you?
自从分手之后
Ever since the relationship ended.
他跟踪我 假装是我的债主
He's been following me around pretending to be a debt collector.
我有次被跟踪了...
I was once stalked...
..被一条狗
...by a dog.
好吧 听着 今天你就放假吧
OK. Look, take the rest of the day
拒接Derek Smeath所有电话
and block all future calls from Derek Smeath.
好的 先生
Yes, sir.
[indistinct chatter on TV]
省着点用啊
Spend it wisely, huh?
哦 天啊 老爸
Oh, God. Dad?
我来就是想跟您谈谈钱的事
Money... is what I came to talk to you about.
是吗? 亲爱的?
Oh, yeah? Hey, honey?
- 是吗? - 因为...
- [woman] Yeah? - Becau...
- 烤翅好了没? - 来喽
- [man] You got them wings? - Coming. [humming]
真是搞笑
It's funny because your mom and I
我跟你妈妈刚想给你打电话
were gonna call you over here today
谈谈钱的事
to talk about pretty much the exact same thing. Money.
- 我们的积蓄 - 我们这辈子的积蓄
- Savings. - Our money. Our life savings.
真的?
Really?
自从结婚以来
[woman] All our married life, we've been the kind of people
我们一心只想着存钱
that we just don't spend, we save.
我们存了点钱
We've built up quite a little nest egg.
- 有个小金库 - 大金库吧
- Of money. - A big nest egg of money.
- 有点小钱 - 是的
- Of dough. - Yeah, we do.
所以我们决定
[man] And so, we decided...
所以我把你
[woman] That we wanted to call you here,
我们可爱的女儿叫过来
our only beautiful,
告诉你
lovely daughter to tell you that, well...
我们把它全花了
[both] We spent it!
一分不剩
[woman] Every last cent.
[? Adrienne Bailon: Big Spender]
他还在学怎样驾驭它
He's still just getting the hang of it.
漂亮吧?
Isn't she a babe?
他一直都想要这个
He's wanted one of these since the day I met him.
里面有食品搅拌器 四台电风扇
It's got a built-in blender, four electric fans,
还有污物碾碎器
and a thermal sewage disposal.
你知道英格兰的Kathy和Gordon吗
Kathy and Gordon, in England,
他们两家的游泳池被霉菌毁了
you know the ones whose pool collapsed because of the mold?
- 大胡子Kathy吗? - 是的
- Kathy with the beard? - Yep.
不过她已经电蚀除毛了
Yes, she had electrolysis.
他们把这网页发给我们
They sent us this off the Web. It's an article about...
是篇关于理财的文章
Makes you think about money.
- 怎样让做到物有所值 - 买养老保险?
- About what it's really worth. - Security in your old age?
还是投资你所爱的?
Or is it investing in what you love?
你真该读读
You have got to read it.
绿围巾女孩写的
It's by someone called The Girl in the Green Scarf.
她真是个天才
She's a genius.
天哪 伙计们 我们进军国际市场了
Oh, my God. Guys! We're international!
耶!
- [all chattering] - Yes!
Luke 我们进驻亚洲了
Luke, we've taken Asia.
RusseII 论按揭经纪人的文章写好了没?
Russell, how's that article on mortgage brokers?
- 一定会引起轰动的 - 账单
- It's gonna be huge. - Paycheck.
- Rebecca? - 谢谢
- Uh, Rebecca? - Thank you.
- 什么事? - 我想你下周
- Yes? - I want you to come with me
跟我去参加APA(美国新闻协会)会议
to the APA Conference next week.
好的 APA会议是什么?
Absolutely. What's the APA Conference?
一年一度的最大的新闻界盛会
The biggest magazine event of the year.
在迈阿密举行
In Miami.
Luke 我觉得我们应该早点去
Oh, Luke. I think I should definitely be there.
早点去找好旅店 饭馆
Early, I mean, and you know, make sure that
以防到时大家都累了
the hotel's OK and find good restaurants in case
也许不一定累了
anyone wants to relax. Not that I intend to,
但谁知道呢
but you never know, some people might.
很高兴你对此很感兴趣
[laughs] I'm glad you're enthusiastic about it.
- 我自己也有些兴奋 - 是吗?
- I'm kind of excited myself. - Oh. You are?
我是说
Yeah, I mean because a lot of people
很多人都急切地想见你
are very excited to meet you.
你开拓了一块新读者人群
You've opened up a whole new demographic.
- 他说你开拓了什么? - 读者人群
- You're opening up his what? - [laughing] Demographic.
- 哦 - 这就是为什么他想带我出去度假
- Mm-hmm. - Which is why he wants to
我是说去参加美国新闻协会会议
take me to the beach. I mean the conference.
你不是一直想进Alette吗?
Aren't you supposed to be getting to Alette?
我正在努力
I'm on my way. Once you're in, you're in.
- 你现在是经济学大师了 - 我给大家提了很多相当棒的建议
- You're in as a finance guru. - I give great financial advice.
Bex 何不给自己点建议呢?
Bex, have you ever considered taking your own advice?
- 哇 - 妈妈 别闹了
- Oh! - Mom, calm.
绿围巾女孩会怎样看待
Like, what would The Girl in the Green Scarf
把账单藏在床下这事?
say about hiding Visa bills under your bed?
- 这两者毫无瓜葛 - 错
- That is not relevant. - That is so relevant.
关系可大了
It's the most relevant thing in the world.
- 啊! - 为什么你这么急着去迈阿密
- Ah! - There isn't another reason
一定还有其它原因吧?
why you want to go to Miami?
- 没啦! - 是不是对FIuke有感觉?
- No! - Maybe it rhymes with Fluke?
他叫Luke
- Luke. - [laughs]
- 怎么啦 - 我猜中了吧
- Wha... - That's it.
- 你在掩饰 - 掩饰什么?
- You're making that face. - What face?
不可思议 Bex 你喜欢上他了
Bex! You like him! This is terrible!
不可能 假设...
No, no. No, no. But hypothetically...
你真是个大骗子
Hypothetically you're being a big, fat liar!
建议别人怎样理财 自己却深陷其中
You're advising people about debt, and you're up to your eyeballs in it.
好的 你藏起来吧
- [groaning] - Yeah, hide under there.
Sherman先生 你好
- [yawing] - Ooh, MonsieurSherman.
我姓Brandon 我妈妈才姓Sherman
My name is Brandon. My mother's name is Sherman.
没错 低调先生
Yes. Monsieurdiscret. Mm-hmm.
- Oh! [laughs] - [chuckles]
- 谢谢 - 没关系
- You saved me. - Not at all.
天哪
Oh, gosh!
你在成功理财上班
You work at Successful Saving.
- 是的 - 我该请你吃顿饭
- Yes. - We should have dinner.
[? Kat DeLuna: Calling You]
我该怎么做?
[Rebecca] OK, what am I supposed to do?
自然点就好了
[Luke] Just be yourself.
- Luke 你好 - 嗨 Luke
- Luke, how are you? - Hey, Luke.
真是太好了 你被释放了
They let you out of prison. That's fantastic.
- AIicia - Luke
- Alicia. - Luke.
容我介绍一下 Rebecca BIoomwood
Can I introduce Rebecca Bloomwood?
也许你们都读过绿围巾女孩的文章吧
You may have read The Girl in the Green Scarf.
你的专栏是?
[man] What's the name of your column?
"风险投资就像一双厚底高跟鞋''
"Risky investment is like a pair of platform boots."
天哪 以前从没人这样抬举过我
Wait, nobody has ever quoted me back to me before.
- Luke 聊聊可以吗? - 好的
- Luke. Got a second? - Yeah. Sure.
对了 你为什么被关押?
Wait, what were you in prison for?
- 被人栽赃的 - 人们很信任你
- Oh, that was trumped-up. - People out there trust you.
投资的蝴蝶效应
- Butterfly investments. - [indistinct chattering]
- 谢谢 - 不客气
- Thanks. - [man] Pleasure.
- 来杯香槟 - 马上 先生
- Champagne, please. - [man] Right away, sir.
嗨 你在北方联合银行上班吧?
Hi. Are you from the United North Bank?
- 我负责这家银行 - 我去过那
- I run it. - I was walking past your bank.
你们的橱窗很乏味
You have the most boring window displays in the world.
- 她说的是反语 - 我认真的
- She means the opposite. - I'm serious.
感觉就像瞌睡虫爬进了脑袋
It's as if somebody hit the snooze button in my brain,
让人昏昏欲睡
and told me it was OK to sleep another ten minutes.
- 是吗 - 真的
- Really. - Yes.
放几把可爱的粉红雨伞之类的
You need to put some pretty pink umbrellas or something
- 吸引人 - Lewis先生 我跟你说
- to get people in. - Mr. Lewis, look here.
知道吗?
Know what else you could do?
- 可以搞个促销活动 - 促销?
- You could have a sale. - A sale?
可以降价促销 免费发甜甜圈之类的
Yes. Fee reductions. And free doughnuts.
她是个幽默的专栏作家 幽默就是她的风格
She writes a humorous column, humor is part of her language.
- 再来杯 - 真是奇思妙想
- I'll get another. - Unusual ideas.
Luke 你的作家有点失态了
Luke, your writer, she's out of control.
你得管管她 不然会坏大事的
Keep her on a leash. She's damaging the magazine.
正好相反 她知道自己在干什么
She doesn't need a leash, I'd say quite the contrary.
你给我的那份耸人听闻的小报是关于什么的?
What was the piece of tabloid sensationalism you sent me?
揭露Jon GoIdma的吗?
The Jon Goldman expose?
那可是一份有根有据的报道
A well-researched, supported article.
报道说他很腐败 满是经济问题
His organization is corrupt, full of financial holes.
他的公司对Dantay-West来说至少值200万
Not running the piece. His company's worth two million to Dantay-West.
- Ryan - Lewis先生
- Ryan. - Mr. Lewis.
Luke 你那专栏作家可真能侃
Luke, that columnist of yours said the most outrageous things.
我道歉
I'd like to apologize for our company.
但她很聪明
Outrageous, yet brilliant things.
她真像一缕清风 很新鲜
She's like a breath of fresh air.
- 我同意 - 同意
- I couldn't agree more. - Totally agree too.
- 他不可能认可 - 我们的橱窗真没意思
- He couldn't agree more. - Our displays are boring.
- 是吗? - 她说得对
- Aren't they? - She's right.
她很直爽 我喜欢她新奇的想法
She's honest. The doughnut idea I loved.
我呆会跟你谈谈广告的事
I'll be talking to you about advertising.
- 好呢 - 好
- Great. - Great.
- 很好 - 不错
- OK. - OK.
干得不错
No, you're doing great.
还有个人你得见见
There's one more person that you really ought to meet.
- 呃 - 这人很挑剔
- Hmm. - This one's pretty crucial,
但你们有共同语言
but having the language in common should help.
语言?
Hmm. Language?
来见见诺基亚的Janne Virtanen
Yeah, I want you to meet Janne Virtanen from Nokia.
我跟他说你会芬兰语
I told him you're part Finnish,
Janne很想见见你
and he's very excited to meet you. Janne.
Rebecca
[stuttering] Rebecca.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Ah. [speaks Finnish] - Hey, hey, hey.
在芬兰 人们就是这样做的
That's how you do it in Finland.
[speaks Finnish]
[speaks gibberish]
- Luke! Luke Brandon! - 他真会搞笑
- [man] Luke! Luke Brandon! - He's really funny.
- 我翻不出那个味来 - 兄弟 很久不见
- I can't even translate that. - Long time no see, buddy.
[speaks Finnish]
我离开芬兰就因为你们这种臭男人
Men like you are the reason I left Finland.
[? Gwen Stefani: Rich Girl plays on cell phone]
- 你好? - 是Bloomwood小姐吗?
- ?Hola? - [Derek] Ms. Bloomwood?
我是城市债务公司的Derek Smeath
It's Derek Smeath from All City Debt Collection.
- 总算找到你了 - 啊
- At last we meet. - Uh.
你的腿咋样了? 好了没?
How's your leg? Still broken?
呃 好多了
Uh... it's, um. It's much better.
- Brandon先生 - 呃
- Mr. Brandon. - Yes.
我们北欧人...喜欢她!
We Scandinavians...
相当喜欢
...like her. A lot.
很好 那你下午就来我办公室
Good. Then kindly limp, stagger, or crawl
不管你就一瘸一拐还是爬过来
to my office this afternoon.
当然
Um, absolutely, I would love to.
很好
Good.
- 但... - 又怎样了?
- Except... Oh, my God. - What?
我姨妈跳伞时出了点意外
My aunt has just fallen from the sky in a freak skydiving accident.
够了
Enough! Unless the outstanding balance is transferred from
周一早上九点到账
your account first thing 9:00 on Monday morning...
- Smeath先生 - 不然
- Mr. Smeath, uh... - ...the next step will be...
我们就只有私下解决
...personal contact.
好的 周一早上九点
Absolutely, 9:00 on Monday morning.
我得挂了 真对不住
I have to go. I'm so sorry. I've got to go.
录个来电铃声
You are getting your own ringtone.
Derek Smeath来电 不要接
[whispering] Do not answer this call, it's Derek Smeath.
- 不要接 - Rebecca
- Do not... [yelps] - Rebecca. Oh!
- 谢谢 - 跟你说个事
- [gasping] Thanks. - I have something to tell you.
我也有事跟你说
[Rebecca] I have something to tell you, too.
好的
OK.
你先说吧
You first.
Edgar Westhas要举行
Well, Edgar West has taken a table at the
新闻协会慈善晚会
Print Association Charity Ball,
猜猜我们杂志哪两个
and guess which two people from Successful Saving
受邀出席?
have been invited as representatives?
这可是莫大的荣幸
It's a huge mark of respect.
这就意味着我们进入了主流杂志的行列
This puts us in the major league,
这一切都要归功于你
and that is mainly down to you.
- 哇 - 你没事吧?
- Huh... - Are you OK?
- 有点难以启齿 - 没事 说吧
- This isn't easy. - OK.
你的领带不搭
Your tie does not go with your shirt.
好好享受吧 享受购物的乐趣
Try to enjoy yourself. No, no, you have to savor shopping.
不行
No, you don't.
你得直击目标然后赶紧走人
You have to strike with precision and get out.
- 嗨 - 你好
- Hi. - Hello.
我们老板要买衣服
We're looking for clothes for my boss.
知道 是要套装还是夹克?
Absolutely. Were you thinking maybe a suit or a jacket?
都要
I'm actually thinking about everything.
好的 我们竭诚为您服务
Oh, well, we can do everything.
天哪 我喜欢男士穿粉红色的 这个怎么样?
Pink. Oh, my gosh, I love pink on a guy. Is that bad?
- 这件不错 - 太棒了
- That pink is great. - It's gorgeous.
- 他适合粉红吗? - 适合
- Would he do pink? - I think so.
跟白色裤子应该很搭吧?
Think he'd do it with like a white pant?
- 很搭 - 事实上
- He'd do that. - [clears throat] Actually!
我正真需要的是
What I really need is a, uh, tuxedo,
三扣的的无尾礼服 48号
say three buttons, size 48 regular,
白衬衣 蓝色的也要
a white dress shirt, I'll try the blue as well,
十号黑皮鞋
and a black vernice shoe in a size ten. And two Advil.
你对Prada很在行啊?
You speak Prada?
偶尔
Occasionally.
你知道怎样着装
But if you know how to dress well,
为什么穿成这样?
why do you come to the office looking like...?
我不想别人根据穿着 牌子 家族来评价我
I don't want to be defined by clothes or labels or family.
为什么会根据家族来评价你?
Why would you be defined by family?
我妈妈是纽约社会名流EIinor Sherman
My mother is Elinor Sherman, New York socialite.
不好意思 你刚才说 你母亲是EIinor Sherman吗?
Excuse me, did you just say that your mother is Elinor Sherman?
她有提过她在欢乐之夜上 穿的衣服是我们的吗?
Did she tell you that we dressed her for the Met gala?
她真有气质
Oh, she just looked stunning.
恭喜你 有这样棒的母亲
Well, congratulations on having such a fabulous mother.
呃 我父母离婚了的
My, uh, parents are divorced.
我在英国长大 跟我爸爸住一起
I grew up in England with my dad.
爸爸很好
He's great.
跟妈妈不同 爸爸很务实
Very down-to-earth, totally different from my mother.
直到成年我才开始接触妈妈
Anyway, she wasn't interested until I was an adult.
也许仅仅是因为她需要我
At which point it was assumed that I'd just fall into line.
继位?
- For the throne? - [laughs]
继承家族事业
Uh, no, for the, um... for the family business.
什么事业?
What's the business?
房产
Owning stuff. Real estate, um,
互联网之类
Internet businesses, um...
- 有线电视公司 - 对不起
- Cable companies... - Oh, sorry. Oh, sorry.
我不想屈服于家族势力
I chose to succeed on my own terms,
只想以自己的方式获取成功
not kowtow to some controlling family.
Dantay-West算什么?
What's Dantay-West?
你对所有的事都有自己的成见吗?
Do you have a take on everything in life?
- 是的 - 很好
- Yes. - Yes.
那你怎么看我呢?
Well, what would your take be on... me?
说吧
Go on.
绿围巾女孩会怎样看Luke Brandon呢?
What would The Girl in the Green Scarf's take be on Luke Brandon?
作为一个投资者 你不咋样滴
As an investment, you pretty much suck.
- 为什么? - 你是个工作狂
- What? - You're a workaholic.
你只会全身心地投入工作  却不懂怎样享用成果
You put in all these hours, but you don't reap the rewards.
这只会使别人获益
It goes into someone else's pocket.
但你是个不错的编辑
But you're a great editor.
这样
And now...
你还真像那么回事
...you look like one.
我喝得太多了
Drank a lot of mojitos. I drank too many mojitos.
我可不是只工作不休息的工作狂
It wasn't always work and no play.
- 谢谢 - 谢谢
- Gracias. - Gracias.
- 干杯 - 干
- Cheers! - Mmm.
大婶 买一把
Oh, porfavor. Pick one.
- 真的么? - 真的
- Mmm? Are you serious? - Mm-hmm.
天哪 我爱死这把了看这把红色的
Oh, my God, I love this one. But look at the red one.
- 很可爱 - 挑一把吧
- The red one's cute. - Pick one.
- 多少钱? - 三元
- ?Cuánto cuesta? - Tres dólares.
这把很不错 简单
No, this is gorgeous. Simple.
- 很好 - 为什么给我买扇子?
- Perfect. - Wait, why'd you buy me a fan?
因为我们要跳舞
Because we're going to dance.
可我不知道怎么跳
Oh, I don't know how to do this kind of dancing.
我知道
I do.
[up-tempo music plays]
好了没?
OK?
我带你
Just follow me.
- No... - Oh.
Oh!
我觉得你应该自己做生意
You know, my instinct is that you should have your own business.
- 你觉得? - 是的
- [laughs] That's your instinct? - Yes.
先生 有你的邮包 需要送上去吗?
Your delivery has arrived, sir. Shall I send it up?
- 不用 我自己带上去 - 好的
- No, I'll take that. - OK.
谢谢
Thank you.
我还觉得 应该把这个带去舞会
My other instinct is that I should take this to the ball.
你不觉得吗?
No? What do you think?
Rebecca
Yeah, you know, Rebecca, about the ball, there's, um...
我有事跟你说
There's something that I need...
终于回来了
Well, finally.
[? The Pussycat Dolls: Bad Girl]
Luke 你去哪儿了?
Luke, where have you been?
我一直在找你 我们约好了一起吃饭的
I've been looking for you. We have a dinner reservation.
购物去了?
Did you go shopping?
是的 Rebecca帮我参考
Oh, oh, yes. Yes, Rebecca's been helping me
买了些舞会的衣服
pick something out for the... ball.
很好 我也去购物了
Oh, that's perfect. I went shopping, too.
我们真是绝配
We're gonna look so major together.
拉你陪我 你不会不高兴吧?
Aren't you glad I convinced you to go with me?
这正是我想说的
That's what I was trying to...
很好 购物很愉快
Oh. Oh, great, well, it'll be so much fun.
我得走了
I'm gonna... I'm gonna go. Great.
Rebecca 别急 等等
Oh, wait, wait, Rebecca. Don't go.
我们只是出去喝点东西  AIicia 你认识的
Just, come out for a drink. You know Alicia, and...
- 一起去吧 - 我很乐意
- Yes, come out for a drink. - I would. I'd love to.
只是我得回去打个电话
I just, um, I have to make some calls.
- 我们纽约见 - 真是不凑巧
- I'll see you in New York. - Too bad.
- 再会 - 晚安
- See ya. - Good night.
[? Trey Songz: Takes Time to Love]
[? Gwen Stefani: Rich Girl plays on cell phone]
- Suze 你好 - 不要回家
- Hey, Suze. - [Suze] Don't come home!
我到家了
I am home.
不要从前门走 Derek Smeath来了
Well, don't come to the front door! It's Derek Smeath.
- 继续走 - Rebecca BIoomwood
- Keep driving! - [Derek] Rebecca Bloomwood.
- 天哪 - 不急
- God, oh, God, oh, God. - Don't panic.
- 天哪 - 你跟他怎么说的?
- Oh, God. - What'd you tell him?
我跟他说Ermintrude姨妈死于痢疾
OK. I told him that your Aunt Ermintrude died of malaria.
我说的是她死于跳伞事故
She died in a skydiving accident.
她的降落伞没打开
Her parachute didn't open.
我怎么知道 你根本就没姨妈
How am I supposed to know? She doesn't even exist!
我犯错了 但我相信生活会好起来的
I know I've made some mistakes, but I'm turning my life around.
我已经计划好了 我要去舞会
I've got it planned. I'm gonna go to the ball.
先给AIette NayIor留个好印象
Impress Alette Naylor.
拿着! 现在我要做的就是买条新裙子
Here! All I have to do first is buy a new dress.
Bex 不行! 不能再买了
Bex, no! Absolutely not.
你已经有1万条裙子了
You've 10,000 dresses already.
什么? 你太夸张了
What? You exaggerate.
我记得有条很漂亮的裙子 不知道你什么时候买的
I know the dress. It's perfect. You got it at the thing.
知道我说的哪条吗? 放哪了?
Know what I'm talking about? Where is it?
希望没有在那次"大扫除"的时候扔掉
I hope we didn't throw it away at the de-cluttering.
噢 Bex 想想你穿这个会有多靓
Oh, Bex. Imagine you wearing this dress.
穿起来秀一秀 是不是想想都很嫉妒?
Walk past the mirror. Would you be jealous?
- 当然! - 是的
- Yes! - Yes.
噢 天呐 我完全忘记这宝贝了
Oh, my gosh, I forgot I even had this dress.
你穿这个会迷倒FIuke的
And Fluke would love you in that dress.
别提FIuke了
Don't talk about Fluke.
怎么了? 出什么事了?
Why? What happened?
一个长腿辣女AIicia出现了
Alicia Bitch Longlegs is what happened.
我讨厌她 她是哪位?
I hate her. Who is she?
一个有长相 有身材的完美女人
She's the girl with the perfect everything.
天哪 Luke就是个大白痴
Well, well, Luke is a raging moron.
等你穿着这身衣服闪亮登场的时候
He's gonna be so bummed when you show up
他肯定会后悔莫及
at the ball looking like a total knockout in that dress.
你绝对会吸引所有人的眼球
You're gonna be a total hottie.
这件太棒了 那现在我得买个新包包来搭
It's perfect. All I have to do now is buy a new bag.
噢 天呐 Bex 这房间里肯定会有那么个包包的
Oh, my God. Bex, there has to be a bag somewhere in this room.
Suze 别打开衣柜!
Suze, do not open that closet!
[Suze screams]
噢 Suze! Suze!
Oh, Suze! Suze!
Suze,  你还好吗? 噢 我的老天
Suze, are you there? Oh. Oh, my God.
原来你一件都没扔 是吗?
You didn't throw anything away, did you?
对不起
I'm sorry.
那好 我知道你该去干嘛了
OK. I know what you need.
我叫Joyce 我是个购物狂
My name is Joyce, and I'm a shopaholic.
- 你好 Joyce - 说说你的故事
- Hi, Joyce. - How's it going?
谢谢 我是一个纺织品进口商的妻子
Thank you. I'm the wife of a textile importer.
我丈夫在衣橱里发现了我的秘密
My husband found my secret stash in the linen closet.
对 他发现了我所有的旅行装
Yeah, he found all of my cruisewear,
现在他说 再不会有旅行了!
and now he says that there won't be a cruise!
- 噢 - 好了 先到这儿吧 Joyce
- Oh. - OK, hang in there, Joyce.
Ryuichi 你呢? 这周怎么样?
What about you, Ryuichi? How was your week?
我叫Ryuichi, 我是个购物狂
My name is Ryuichi, and I'm shopaholic.
你好 Ryuichi
[all] Hi, Ryuichi.
距离我上次刷卡已经有
It is six months, three weeks
6个月 3周 4天了
and four days since I last used my credit card.
- 天呐! - Ryuichi!
- Oh! - Ryuichi!
真是太棒了 你是我们大家的榜样
That is just wonderful. You're an inspiration to all of us.
你听到了吗 Joyce?
Did you hear that, Joyce?
那么你呢 Freak先生?
What about you, Mr. Freak?
我叫D. Freak 嗯 我是个购物狂
My name is D. Freak. Uh, I'm a shopaholic.
- 你好 Freak - 欢迎
- Hi, Freak. - Welcome.
我也是个前NBA球员
I'm also a former NBA player.
言归正传 今天我在卡地亚又失去控制了
We'll get back to that. Um, I cracked at Cartier today.
这次买了多少?
How many did you buy this time?
嗯...7件
Uh... I got seven.
我给一周的每一天都买了
One for every different day of the week.
看 这个Santos腕表 还有...
See, I got the Santos. And I got...
还是言归正传 好吗? 给他一点鼓励 我们继续
Keep comin' back, OK? Give him some support. Keep comin' back.
哪家店?
Which store?
Rebecca 到你来说说了
Rebecca, why don't you share your story.
嗯... 大家好 嗯 我是Rebecca BIoomwood
Um... Hello, everybody. Uh, I'm Rebecca Bloomwood.
你好 Rebecca
[all] Hi, Rebecca.
我来这完全是为了我的朋友
I just actually came here as a favor to a friend.
嗯 我的意思是 我喜欢购物
Uh, I mean, I like shopping.
喜欢购物有什么错?
Is there anything so wrong with that?
商店就是让人去享受的
I mean, stores are put there to enjoy.
嗯 买东西的感觉太棒了
Uh, the experience is enjoyable.
哇 不止是太棒
Well, more than enjoyable.
简直...太美好了
It's... It's beautiful.
模特身上丝绸的光泽
The sheen of silk, draped across a mannequin.
意大利皮鞋的味道
Oh, the smell of new Italian leather shoes.
意大利皮鞋 那是最棒的
Italian leather shoes, that's the best.
哦...那种要刷卡的冲动
Oh... The rush you feel when you swipe your card.
只要刷了卡 就都属于自己了!
And it's approved. And it all belongs to you!
好了 Rebecca 谢谢你的故事
OK, Rebecca. Thank you for sharing.
当你买了什么的时候 就会非常快乐
The joy you feel when you've bought something,
购物就像天堂
and it's just you and the shopping.
- 购物就是天堂 - Ryuichi!
- You and shopping. - Ryuichi!
通向天堂只需要小小的信用卡
All you have to do is hand over a little card.
- 太对了! - 别说了!
- Yes! - Pull it together!
谁敢说那种感觉不是最美的?
Isn't that the best feeling in the world?
- 是的 - 甚至想...
- Yeah. - Don't you wanna
- 跑到山顶大呼过瘾 - 就是这种感觉
- shout it from the mountaintops? - That's real talk.
你感觉如此地... 自信并且活力四射...
And you feel so... confident and alive...
- 开心? - 对 开心!
- And happy? - And happy!
- 温暖 - 还有温暖!
- And warm. - And warm!
- 大家都怎么了? - 我要买个新包包
- What's going on here? - I need to buy a new bag.
- 我得给AIette NayIor留下完美印象 - 再买块手表搭配
- I have to impress Alette Naylor. - Get a watch to go with that bag.
哦 Catherine MaIandrino在打折
Oh, there's a sale at Catherine Malandrino.
- 我就是这么想的 - 别让她...
- You're like my soul sister. - Don't let her...
我得抓紧时间了 大伙再见
I have to go. Good luck, everybody.
那儿有鞋吗?
[stuttering] They have shoe?
- 你们坐下 - 我要坚定意志
- You sit down. - [all] My will is strong.
我要看好钱包 我不要购物
My wallet is closed. I do not want to shop.
[? Amy Winehouse with Hot Chip: Rehab]
噢!
Ah!
噢 这盒子里是什么? 还会有惊喜吗?
Oh, what's in this box? Have I seen absolutely everything?
Sparkles(诗伯高)  噢 我爱死Sparkles了
[gasping] Sparkles. Oh, I love sparkles.
仓库里还有吗?
Do you have any more in the back?
是你! 噢!
You. You! Oh!
抱歉
I'm sorry.
把这些都拿走! 都拿走!
Get it away from me! Get it all away from me!
这双不用! 噢 我的上帝
Not those! Oh, my God.
[car horns honking]
[Muzak rendition of Rehab plays]
[indistinct chattering]
AIicia! 你可真是星光闪耀
Alicia! Mmm. You look stunning.
嘿 介绍一下 这位是Luke Brandon
Hey. I want you to meet Luke Brandon.
- "成功理财"杂志社的 - 那本杂志很不错
- From Successful Saving. - The magazine looks great now.
她就在那儿 好的 别紧张
[Rebecca] There she is. OK, do not panic.
你好 Alette
Hello, Alette.
我14岁就想到你的杂志社工作...
Since I was 14 I wanted to work at your magazine...
Rebecca 你挺可爱啊
Rebecca. You look so cute.
- 衣服脱线了 - 什么?
- You're unraveling. - What?
- 见鬼 - 丢人呐
- [gasps] What? - Tsk. Shame.
你好
- Hi. - [indistinct chattering]
- [sleeve ripping] - [yells]
天呐!
- Oh! [yells] - [screams]
[both shouting]
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我的天呐 天呐 天呐
Oh, please. Oh, no. Oh, no.
- 她很可爱 不是吗? - 是的 很可爱
- Isn't she adorable? - Uh, yes. Adorable.
噢 噢!
Oh, oh, oh!
哇!
Woo!
亲爱的 给我来杯香槟
Now, dear. I need a glass of champagne right now.
- 马上就来 - 我要加汤力水的杜松子酒
- Coming right up. - And I'll have a gin and tonic.
马上来
Absolutely.
我可是非常想见那位"戴绿围巾的女孩"
I'm intrigued to meet this Girl in the Green Scarf.
- 听说会是未来的电视明星 - 对 是的
- Potential TV star, I hear. - That's right, yes.
他们想让她上"早间咖啡"节目
They want her on the Morning Coffee show.
Rebecca上电视肯定会非常漂亮
I think Rebecca would be great on television.
想不吸引眼球都难
She's... She's hard to ignore.
- 打扰一下! - 那些菜都装好盘了?
- Excuse me! - Are those plates presentable?
- 装得很好 - 不用说话! 快上菜!
- Plates are beautiful. - Do not talk back! Take it and go!
然后收拾好餐桌 动作快点! 快点!
Bus your tables, come right back! Move it!
我应该读读"戴绿围巾的女孩"
I should read this Green Scarf Girl.
她现在好像很火 嗯?
It seems she's very à la mode, hmm?
- 是这样 - 嘿!
- Real poise. - Hey!
你是谁? 你在干嘛?
What are you? What are you doing?
噢 我要加汤力水的杜松子酒 还有一些香槟
Oh. I need a gin and tonic and some champagne, please.
你是谁 酒鬼? 把酒放回去!
What are you, a drunk? Put that back!
快过来 金发姑娘
On your feet, Goldilocks.
没看见我们人手不够?
Do you know how short-staffed we are?
- 快去上菜 快去! - 不 不 我得...
- I need food on tables now. Go! - No, no, no. I need to get...
- 再来6盘! - 噢! 我不是服务员
- Six more, please! - Oh! I'm not a waitress.
宝贝 我知道你不是 你是演员 我明白
I know you're not, honey. You're an actress. I get it.
我明白了 快去 快 快!
I do. Now go, go, go, go, go!
还杵在这干嘛? 把鱼拿给客人!
What are you doing? Go out there and serve the fish!
- 噢! - 你! 给这桌上菜 快点
- Oh! [screams] - You! Serve this table. Do it.
- BIoomwood小姐 - 是
- Ms. Bloomwood. - Yes.
- 我要鳟鱼 - 我要三文鱼
- I'll have the trout, please. - I'll have the salmon.
- 哪种低脂调料做的鱼吗? - 我不是服务员
- Do you have low-fat dressing? - I'm not a waitress.
- BIoomwood小姐! - 给 三文鱼
- Ms. Bloomwood! - OK. Salmon here.
- 这就是大名鼎鼎的BIoomwood小姐? - 服务员小姐?
- This is the famous Ms. Bloomwood? - The waitress?
BIoomwood小姐! 把那些放下 过来坐!
Ms. Bloomwood! Just put it down and sit!
坐 噢!
Sit. Oh!
[shouting]
对不起 对不起 太抱歉了 噢!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. Sorry. Oh!
- 坐下Rebecca - Jacket!
- Sit down, Rebecca. - Jacket!
好了 女士们先生们 今晚我们供应...
Right, uh, ladies and gentlemen, tonight we will be serving...
嗯 溪红点鲑 和烟熏三文鱼
...the, uh, brook trout and wild smoked salmon.
West太太 您肯定会很高兴
Mrs. West, you'll be pleased to hear that the fish from this region
因为这里的鱼可是很有催情作用的
is a particularly powerful aphrodisiac.
- 噢 - 嗯 给她两份
- Oh. - Mmm. Give her two.
Brandon先生  你当服务员也相当专业啊
Oh, Mr. Brandon, you serve as if you've served all your life.
噢 我的大学学费就是当服务生挣的
Oh, paid my way through college waiting tables.
而且很巧 这鱼和您上一期的封面女郎
Coincidentally, that fish weighs the same
- 是一样重的 - 噢!
- as the girl on your last cover. - Ooh!
噢 AIicia 你是鳟鱼还是三文鱼来着?
Oh, Alicia, remind me. Were you a salmon or a trout?
她是鳟鱼(与婆娘同音)
You were a trout.
噢...谢谢你刚刚帮我救场
Oh... Thanks for saving me in there.
为你的相框找到照片了吗?
So have you filled your photo frames yet?
不 还没有
No. Not yet.
其实AIicia的照片挺合适的
You could put a picture of Alicia in one.
除非没有足够的地方
Except there probably wouldn't be room
放她那双蜘蛛腿般细长的双腿
for her spidery long legs.
你知道吗 我总觉得
You know, I've always felt that
"蜘蛛腿般细长"是不是太夸张了
spidery long legs were vastly overrated.
我以为她是你的女朋友
I thought she was your girlfriend.
不 不是
No. She's not my girlfriend.
她不是你
She's not you.
Erica 你打电话给她
Erica, you get her on the phone,
假装她是你全世界最好的朋友
you pretend she's your best friend in the world.
然后弄明白她是怎么搞成现在这样子
You find out how she got in this terrible situation.
她是怎么弄得这么惨?
How did she get so far behind?
都弄明白了之后 就用那些攻击她
Then you take that information and you use it against her.
她为什么那么做? 是骄傲?
What are her motivators? Pride?
诚实? 荣誉? 还是恐惧?
Integrity? Honor? Fear?
告诉她 她将会一无所有 把她的房子弄来抵押
Tell her she'll lose everything. Slap a lien on her house.
告诉她我们还会曝光给媒体
Tell her we'll print it in the papers.
把她逼到悬崖边
Gotta take her to the edge of the cliff.
让她以为你会把她推下去 然后在最后一秒 把她拉回来
Let her think you're gonna push her over and at the last minute,
这样就能拿到你想要的了
pull her back and get what you want out of her.
而且Erica 你的佣金就是这么来的
That, Erica, is how you earn a commission.
就到这 "成功理财"杂志社在几楼?
Lesson over. I need Successful Saving.
就到这 I need Successful Saving.
不好意思
Excuse me.
[elevator bell rings]
- [elevator bell rings] - [cell phone dialing]
[? Batman Theme on cell phone]
我是Derek Smeath 喂? 喂...
Derek Smeath. Hello? Hello...
信号还真差 电梯里面
Elevators. Thank goodness for redial.
别接电话 是Derek Smeath
[cell phone] Do not answer this call, it's Derek Smeath.
Do not answer this call, it's Derek Smeath.
别接电话 是Derek Smeath
别接电话 是...
Do not answer this call, it...
不 他还不知道 但是会的 好的
No, he doesn't know it yet, but he will. All right.
- 回头再说 - Luke! Luke
- Speak to you then. - Luke! Luke.
- 早上好 - 你好
- Good morning. - Hi.
- 你好 - 打扰一下
- Hi. - Excusez-moi.
我来的不是时候? 嗯?
Am I interrupting something? Hmm?
- 不 嗯 - 不 不
- No. Mm-mm. - No, no.
我来找"戴绿围巾的女孩"
I've come for the Green Scarf Girl.
- 我? - 我们尊敬的Monsieur West先生
- Me? - Our esteemed MonsieurWest
让我为你挑套衣服 迎接荧幕初亮相
has asked me to dress you for your TV debut.
我有一小时陪你
I have one hour to shop.
哦 抱歉打扰
Oh, uh, I'm sorry, excuse me,
Rebecca  Derek Smeath来了
but, Rebecca, Derek Smeath is here.
天呐 嗯... 我 嗯...
God. Um... I, uh...
Rebecca一直被他骚扰
Rebecca is being stalked.
"成功理财"故事很多啊
[gasps] So exciting at Successful Saving.
我受够这小丑了 我去见他
I've had enough of this clown. I'll see him.
哇! Luke! 不! 我不想让你见他 不
Whoa! Luke! No! I never want you to meet him, ever.
别担心 我已经叫了保安
Don't worry. I've already called security.
听见了? 她叫了保安
See? She called security.
那我们可以走了吗? 嗯?
Voilà. Shall we go? Mmm?
不 不 不 不
No. No, no, no, no.
这太野蛮了! 我有权利呆在这里
This is outrageous! I have every right to be here.
那个舞会之后 实际上我自己
So after the ball, I, myself, actually
读了你们的杂志 你的文章的确不错
read Successful Saving. Your piece was very good.
我一直在关注你
I have been observing you
你好像是个街头潮流先锋
and it seems you have natural street fashion,
但是... 你有自己真正的风格吗?
but... do you have genuine style?
穿着打扮也是一件非常值得做的事
Dressing is like any worthwhile endeavor.
是艺术 也是挑战
It is an art, but also a challenge.
您好
Bonjour.
这件很适合你 是吗?
This dress is good for you, huh?
然后...加上这件上衣
With maybe... this jacket over.
哇 太棒了AIette
Oh, that's genius, Alette. Parfait.
那套很不错 嗯 但是我觉得...
I think that is a great dress, um, but I was thinking...
...或许...
...a little more...
...像这件... 也不错?
...of something... like this?
然后配上Yves Saint Laurent的外套
I mean, I'd pair it with a new Yves Saint Laurent coat.
穿上看看
Show me.
Rebecca 嗯
So, Rebecca, hmm.
帮她拿着
Take her bag.
你确定穿这个?
You are sure of your choice?
- 对 - 好吧 穿来看看
- Yeah. - Hmm. We'll see.
[gasping]
别接电话 是Derek Smeath
[cell phone] Do not answer this call, it's Derek Smeath.
Do not answer this call, it's Derek Smeath.
别接电话 是Derek Smeath
别接电话 是...
Do not answer this call, it's...
喂
Hello.
啊 很不错
Ah, yes. Is perfect.
好了 现在我得走了
So, unfortunately, I cannot stay.
但我很期待看你怎么搭配
But I am looking forward to seeing how you accessorize it
- 去上电视 嗯? - 哦 谢谢
- for your TV debut. Hmm? - Oh, thank you.
再见
Goodbye.
- 噢 天哪 - 太贵了?
- Oh, God. - Is there a problem?
几乎是我第一个月的薪水
Pretty much my entire first month's salary.
嗯 但是很值 不是吗?
Mmm. But isn't it worth it?
好的 不要偷看 别偷看 你看得见吗? 站上来
OK, no peeking. Don't peek. Can you see? OK. Get up here.
转过来 好了 别偷看哦 别偷看 好了 看呐!
Now turn this way. OK, don't peek. Don't peek. OK, open!
哦 看看 看看! 最漂亮的地方!
Oh, and look, look, look! The best part!
- 你喜欢吗? - 太合适了!
- Do you love it? - It's so her!
哦 Bex 我太高兴了
Oh, Bex. This is so exciting.
我要结婚了 你也喜欢你的伴娘裙
I'm getting married and you love your dress,
而且你也要为Alette工作了 还有...
and you're getting to Alette, and...
那包里的是什么?
What's in that bag?
噢 是AIette为我选的衣服
Oh, that's just a dress that Alette chose for me
为电视节目准备的
for the TV show.
妈妈 你能去拿个杯形蛋糕吗?
Mom, can you go get a cupcake?
那个多少钱?
How much did it cost?
AIette可以享受很低的折扣的
Alette gets an incredible discount.
你还在参加匿名戒购物会吗?
Still going to Shopaholics Anonymous?
当然!
Yes!
- 你说过会去的 - 我知道!
- 'Cause you promised. - I know!
噢 不好意思 你是去购物狂"聚会"吗?
Oh, excuse me. Are you going to the shopaholics meeting?
对
Yes.
你能帮我个忙 暂时把这个放到你的车里吗?
Could you do me a favor and stow these in your trunk?
拿着Barneys的袋袋到克制消费的团队里
Doesn't look good entering a self-help shopping group
似乎不太好
carrying a Barneys bag.
噢! 我懂你的意思
Oh! I know exactly what you mean.
- 给我吧 - 好的
- Leave it to me. - OK.
- 嘿 给我占个座 - 好的
- Hey, save me a seat, huh? - OK.
谢谢!
- [Rebecca] Thank you! - [church bells tolling]
我是Korch女士 我是你们这个团队新的负责人
My name is Ms. Korch. I am your new group leader.
我的处事方式和上任不太一样
I do things differently.
BIoomwood小姐?
Ms. Bloomwood?
你愿意花钱买一些
You're willing to give away your money for things
你不需要的东西 那么怎么不试试
that you don't need, so why not try giving away
把你不需要的东西无偿捐出去
the things you don't need for no money.
但这个是例外: 我真的很需要这个
But here's the thing: I really need those things.
我会告诉你谁最需要它
I'll show you who really needs them.
冷静! 冷静 勇敢点 女士
Steady! Steady. Courage, woman.
- 噢 色彩斑斓 - 这是我的伴娘裙
- Oh, my. Colorful. - This is my bridesmaid's dress.
好了! 有多少人用过这个理由 嗯?
Please! How many of us have used that one before, hmm?
那么 你把这条裙子拿了  然后... 做点好事
OK. I just want you to take these clothes and... do good.
BIoomwood小姐 是不是感觉解脱了? 太棒了!
Ms. Bloomwood, wasn't that liberating? Bravo!
[all cheering]
我要坚定意志 我要看好钱包 我不想购物!
My will is strong. My wallet is closed. I don't want to shop!
我们回去 真是太高兴了
Back to the basement. I couldn't be prouder.
关于我捐的那两条裙子 可能有点误会
There's been a mistake. The dresses I gave in?
- 嗯 我想要回来 - 我知道了 Christy!
- Hmm. I need it back. - I see. Mm-hmm. Christy!
什么事?
Yes?
那两条裙子不能卖了
Can't sell those two dresses. There's been a mistake.
- 不能退的 - 我真的需要那些裙子!
- No returns. - I really need these dresses!
我明天再拿点别的东西来
I'd bring back something tomorrow.
- 更好的 - 我们不换
- Something better. - No exchanges.
- 好 那我买回来 - 真的? 太好了
- OK, so, um, I'll buy 'em. - You will? Oh, that's great.
每分钱我们都需要
Oh, really. We need every cent here.
- 多少钱? - 110
- OK. How much? - A hundred and ten.
什么? 慈善商店还这么贵?
What? How is this a charity store?
这可是Barneys的正品
This is from Barneys.
我知道 我的钱不够买两件
I know. OK, I don't have enough for both.
- 这件才20 - 要不你下次再来买这件?
- This one's twenty. - Maybe come back for this one?
哪件更重要?
Which is more important?
您有理财烦恼吗? 谁没有呢?
Got money issues? Who hasn't?
啊! Tarkie... 到她了!
Oh! Tarkie, Tarkie, Tarkie, she's on!
- 就是这个节目? - 嗯哪
- This is her? - Yeah.
绿围巾女孩 Rebecca Bloomwood
The Girl in the Green Scarf, Rebecca Bloomwood,
她看起来很象专家 对不 她戴的配饰怎么样?
Oh, she looks like an expert. How are her accessories?
嘿 Janice 她在... 哪个频道?
Hey, Janice. She's in the... Whoa. What channel?
理财 我一点不在行
...finance. Not my thing.
- Jane - 什么事?
- Jane. - [Jane] Yeah?
- Janey Janey! - 怎么了?
- Janey. Janey! - What?
然后我读了你的专栏 感觉就象...
[woman on TV] ...then I read your columns, and I'm like...
"天哪 终于开窍了"
"Wow. I get it."
说到点子上了
Right. Which is exactly the point.
因为多数财经报道都很...
Because so much financial journalism is really...
- 都很无趣 - 真是深有同感!
- Is really boring. - I'm with ya on that!
说得好! 继续 Bex!
Yes! Go, Bex!
财经报道让人费解
It's not accessible.
但需要理财的还是普通老百姓
But it's ordinary people that have the most money in savings.
确实 就象我父母一样的普通人
It is. It's people like my mom and dad.
啊!
Ow!
你专栏中写到大衣 和我们说说...
Tell us about the coat. Tell the audience what you wrote
"羊绒大衣及其价值"的寓意
about the cashmere coat and worth.
- 还是你来说吧 - 不 不
- Well, that's you. - No, no.
- 是他给我的灵感 - 哦...
- He inspired me. - Aw...
价格和价值是有区别的
[Rebecca] It's the difference between cost and worth.
从本质上来说 价值看不见摸不着
Essentially, something you can't see, can't touch,
实际上 美国最无价的商品
but it's actually the most valuable commodity in America.
- 是... - 信任
- And that's... - Trust.
信任 我超爱你们
Trust. I'm loving you guys.
谁会想到债务也能这么有趣呢
Who knew that debt could be so much fun, huh?
我们还有一些时间
But we just have a little bit more time.
留给观众提问
We wanna get questions from the audience.
在座有没有人
Is there anybody out there
有理财烦恼 想与...
with any financial issues that would like...
好 就你吧 先生
Yes, you, sir.
我有些债务麻烦
Well... I'm having trouble with debt.
好 房贷 车贷?
OK. Mortgage debt, car debt?
- BIoomwood小姐的债务 - BIoomwood小姐的债务
- Ms. Bloomwood's debt. - [laughs] Ms. Bloomwood's debt.
没错
That's right.
我来自"城市收债代理机构"
I'm from the All City Debt Collection Agency.
- 我叫Derek Smeath - 好
- My name is Derek Smeath. - [woman] Alrighty.
上帝啊 这个人
Now, look, for God's sake, can I just say that this man
对Rebecca纠缠一年之久
has been stalking Rebecca for the past year.
没错
Yes, I have.
就是想结清她的信用卡所欠款项
To recover unrepaid credit on a store card totaling
9412.25美元
$9,412 and a quarter.
这是真的?
- [audience gasps] - Is this for real?
不好意思 他是她的前男友
No, I'm sorry, because he is her ex-boyfriend.
真的?
Really?
难怪她没把他带回来过
No wonder she didn't bring him home.
真强啊
That's good. I tell ya,
看看我 你们相信我是她前男友吗?
the more you look at me, the funnier that gets.
好吧 我的前女友
OK, well, uh, my ex-girlfriend
告诉我她今天不能见我
told me she couldn't meet me today
因为她在芬兰染上了传染病
because I might risk contamination with an infection
- 可能会传染给我 - 哦!
- she picked up in Finland. - Oh!
你知道她有芬兰血统吗?
[Derek] Know she was part Finnish?
好 我们时间不多了
- [audience laughs] - OK, we're on limited time.
有没有其他观众想...
Anybody else like to ask...
别 别 精彩的还在后面呢
No, no, no. The best is yet to come.
上帝啊!
Oh, God!
你们知不知道这位Bloomwood小姐
Did you realize our Ms. Bloomwood here
现在正因为忧郁症住院治疗?
is in the hospital with depression?
现在正因为胆结石住院治疗?
Currently in the hospital with gallstones.
"支票已寄" 14次
"Check is in the mail" 14 times.
- "支票在邮递中丢失" 14次 - 有没有其他观众提问?
Check is lost in the mail 14 times.
"化学果酸脱皮康复中"
Recovering from a chemical fruit acid peel.
被召回再次出差 目的地:巴士拉 (伊拉克东南部港市)
Called back for second tour of duty in Basra.
[laughter]
这些借口哪个是真的?
Which of these excuses is true?
有没有一个是真的?
Are any of them?
请真实的Rebecca BIoomwood起立
Will the real Rebecca Bloomwood please stand up?
起码我不用再担心你被纠缠之事了!
Well, at least I don't have to worry about you being stalked!
Luke 你不明白!
Luke, you don't understand!
没错 我是不明白!
No, you're right, I don't!
发挥一下职业精神 Rebecca
So do what I hired you to do, Rebecca,
澄清事实
and make the truth clear
给完全不明白的我一个交待
to somebody who absolutely doesn't understand.
我喜欢购物
I shop.
你撒谎就因为你喜欢购物
Oh, so you lie because you shop.
好 你为什么喜欢购物?
- [stammering] - OK, OK. Why do you shop?
- 我... - 说啊!
- Well, I... - Come on, come on!
你要给我点时间...
Well, you're not giving me time...
给你时间作什么? 让你再胡编乱造?
For what? To make something up?
你就不能说一次真话?
Just, for once in your life, tell me the truth.
因为购物时 世界变得更美好
Because when I shop, the world gets better.
世界确实变得更美好了
The world is better.
但后来又不美好了 我就再去购物
And then it's not anymore. And I need to do it again.
你的诚实呢?
Well, what about honesty?
你的信用呢?
What about credibility?
我本想告诉你的
Well, I wanted to tell you,
但我接受这份工作只是为了要进Alette
but I only took the job to get to Alette.
希望你愿望成真
Well, I wish you all the best with that.
Luke 真是对不起
Luke, I'm so sorry.
不用 我了解 整件事就是一个谎言
No, no. I understand. The whole thing was a lie.
现在终于明白了
That absolutely makes sense.
* 你伤了我的心 你将它撕碎 *
[woman] ? You're breaking my heart You're tearing it apart
* 呜 呜 *
? Woo, woo
* 现在我已变得疯狂 *
? Now I've gone insane
* 你把我的眼镜也打碎 好吗? *
? And you're breaking my glasses, too, OK?
她穿的是我的伴娘服?
Is she wearing my bridesmaid's dress?
Suze!
- [door slams] - Suze!
我可以解释的!
That, I can absolutely explain!
好! 解释吧
OK! Explain.
Oh...
解释啊!
Explain!
Suze!
West先生 我很喜欢Luke Brandon
Mr. West. I like Luke Brandon.
但依最近的态势看来 Brandon先生
But it would seem on recent evidence, Mr. Brandon
已经失去了其客观判断力
allowed his objectivity to lapse.
Brandon先生?
Mr. Brandon?
[sighs]
Rebecca BIoomwood...
Rebecca Bloomwood...
Rebecca BIoomwood是我见过的 最有生气的
Rebecca Bloomwood was the most vivacious,
最有趣最能鼓舞人心的女子
funny, inspiring woman I have ever met.
现在我们知道 她的生活是个谎言
And she lived a lie. We know that now.
但她在专栏中写的都是事实
But what she wrote in her columns was the truth.
她有见解
She had a voice.
她能让那些不懂财经的人读懂
She spoke to people who never believed
而他们一旦读懂
that they could understand, and who loved it when
就爱上她的文章 我也超爱
they found that they could. And I loved it.
Rebecca BIoomwood让我失望
Rebecca Bloomwood let me down.
但绿围巾女孩却从没有
But the Girl in the Green Scarf never did.
[horn plays up-tempo tune]
至于你 如果Luke Brandon及其态度
As for you, if Luke Brandon and his attitude
不能胜任Dantay-West的工作
aren't fitting in at Dantay-West,
就只有一种解决办法
there's really only ever one solution.
或许我们应该开办一家全新的杂志
Maybe we should start a new magazine.
一家完全发表作家见解的杂志
A magazine driven purely by the voices of its writers.
隶属于公司 但另立门户 明白么?
A part of the company, but outside the gates, you know?
听起来...不错
Yeah, sounds... Sounds great.
让人意外 但 你知道...
Yeah. It's unexpected, but, you know.
你有干劲 Brandon先生 也有远见
You have drive, Mr. Brandon, and vision.
我很赞赏
I've been impressed.
创办新刊会很艰辛
Oh, it'll be tough going to start,
但Cy和我创办公司也是这么过来的
but that's the way Cy and I built this company.
我们把公司名挂在门上的那一天 Dantay-West
On the day that we put that sign up over the door, Dantay-West.
就知道这一决定是正确的
That was when we knew that we'd made the right decision.
为新杂志干杯
So here's to our new venture.
呃 我...
Well, I, um. I can't...
真不敢相信 我要杀了她
I cannot believe it. I'm going to kill her.
West先生 当您把公司名挂在门上时
Mr. West, when you put that sign above the door,
您是想让它享誉全球吧?
you wanted to make your name in the world, didn't you?
- 这是我最大的愿望 - 我也是
- Oh, more than anything else. - So do I.
亲爱的 她会没事的
[Jane] Sweetie, she's gonna be fine.
你去和她谈时 不要...
And when you talk to her, don't...
亲爱的 实话实说 你觉得...
Sweetie, honestly, do you think it's too...
"培养有经济头脑的孩子"
"Raising Financially Fit Kids."
你觉得现在给她这本书是不是太晚了?
Do you think it's too late for this?
亡羊补牢 犹为未晚  去书展难道你不高兴吗?
Never too late. Aren't you glad we went to that book fair?
很美 是不是?
Pretty amazing, ain't it?
所以你妈和我就爱来这儿
That's why your mother and I love coming out here.
总能让我们想起在芬兰渡过的童年
Reminds us of our childhood in Finland.
你妈和我觉得
Your mom and I think,
美国经济欠债几十亿
if the American economy can be billions in debt
都能挺过难关 你也能
and still survive, so can you.
- 那车大约值13... - 不行 爸爸
- The RV's worth about 1 3... - No. Dad.
我们想这么做
We want to.
如果你把车卖了 我就杀了你
I will kill you if you sell it.
车诠释了你 你的全部
It completely defines you. Completely.
没有东西能诠释我 除了你和你妈
Nothing defines me, except you and your mother.
[? Greg Laswell: Girls Just Wanna Have Fun]
"婚前去父母家 你的烂东西都在你房间"
她真是这样? 而且还达到目的了
So she really did it? And it all worked.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
你是说你不知道
You mean you don't know.
真是好哇
Oh, this is good.
AIette NayIor要去见这位绿围巾女孩
Alette Naylor is going to see the little green scarf girl
把她最想要的工作给她
to give her the one thing that she wants most in all the world.
我是没办法摆脱她了
And now I'm stuck with her.
很高兴能找到你
[Alette] I'm very happy to have found you.
- 我去找了West先生... - 小心烫
- I went to Mr. West to... - Hot.
谢谢 哦 查尔斯和黛安娜
Ah. Thank you. Charles et Diana.
不 不是印第安那人 是英国人 (老爸听错了)
No, no. They're not from Indiana, they're from England.
不是 爸爸 她是说查尔斯和黛安娜
No, Dad, she said Charles and Diana.
我去找West先生 让他宽大处理
Yes. Well, I went to see Mr. West to petition for clemency...
- 他同意了 - Luke Brandon还好吗?
- ...which he gave. - And is Luke Brandon OK?
很不幸  Brandon先生不再为Dantay-West效力了
Unfortunately, Monsieur Brandon is no longer with Dantay-West.
他会没事的
But he'll land on his feet.
怎么说他也是Sherman家族的人  Rebecca...
He's a Sherman, after all. Rebecca...
你可能还不知道 你在电视上的露面
You may not know this, but your appearance
引发了许...多女孩的同感
on that TV show has struck a nerve with many, many girls.
她们同情并理解你
They identify with you.
你的专栏就叫"实惠时尚"
Your column will be Affordable Fashion.
每月一文 500字 欢迎加入Alette
Five hundred words once a month. Welcome to Alette.
我懂实惠时尚
[gasps, laughing] I can do affordable fashion.
我知道所有的打折商品
I mean, I know where all the sales are.
没错 她知道的
Yes, yes, she does. Oh!
实际上 都是我告诉她的
In fact, she got that from me.
不是 不是...
No, I didn't. I didn't. I didn't, I didn't, I didn't.
- 来点蛋糕? - 好
- Oh, cake? - Yes.
别 别!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
要小 小 非常小
Tiny, tiny, tiny, tiny, tiny, tiny.
- 好 - 再小一点! 再小一点!
- Oh. - No, tiny. Tiny! Tiny!
嗯
Hmm.
谢谢
Thank you.
你的专栏要有自己的见解
You will make your column personal.
就写你自己的衣柜
Mm-hmm.
You'll take pieces from your own wardrobe,
就象这个 这很漂亮
like this for example. This is very pretty.
- 很入时 - 当季流行款 我相信
- They're swell. - This season, I believe.
这鞋是Louboutins牌子
Um, well, they're Louboutins,
不能算是实惠时尚
so, I mean, well, they're not affordable fashion.
别担心 我们会把价格印得小小的
Fear not. Chez Alette, we print the prices very small.
毕竟 要信用卡是作什么用的呢?
And after all, what are credit cards for, huh?
你一定深谙其道
You must know that.
是啊
Yeah, wow.
我...深知信用卡
Yeah, no, I, um... I know all about credit cards.
最后通告 催债人
And final notices and debt collectors.
时尚杂志应该把这个也印上 对不?
Um, they should print that in the fashion magazines. Right?
Mm-hmm.
Rebecca 你有道德良知
Rebecca, you have a moral conscience.
但如果你真想为我的杂志效力...
But if you want to work for my magazine...
不 不 我非常想为Alette工作
No, no, I really... I wanna work at Alette.
怎么了 宝贝?
What's the matter, baby?
只不过 我的内心深处有种讨厌的感觉
I just, I have that really annoying feeling in the pit of my stomach.
你们知道这种感觉吗?
You know that feeling when...?
我知道 我知道 我脑中也会有这种感觉
Yes. I get it... I get it in the back of my head.
就是... 你知道不?
[Rebecca] Yeah, when... You know what I mean?
你想做某事 但又觉着你不该那么做?
You wanna do something, but you sort of feel like you shouldn't?
- 就是那样! - 我懂了 就是心病
- That's it! - I get heartburn.
我犯过很多错误
I just... I have made so many mistakes,
我觉得 接受这份工作会是又一个错误
and I feel like taking this job would be another one.
在你做决定之前 你应该知道
Before you make your decision, you should know this.
当我离开这里 机会也会随我而去
When I leave this house, the opportunity leave with me.
那你还是带着你的机会走吧
Well, then you should both go.
这就是生活
C'est la vie.
你可是Sherman家族的
- [phone rings] - [man] You're a Sherman.
你就不能自己筹资吗?
Can't you finance this yourself?
我想知道 你是否会支持我
I'm asking if you will back me.
我想知道 你是否觉得我有投资价值
I'm asking if I am a good investment.
好 伙计们 就这样 你们要把它看作
All right, people, this is it. I want you to think of it
是伏在你身上的有害小猴子
as a toxic little monkey on your back.
快动手 疯子! 谁掉眼泪
Do it, Freak! But anybody who cries
就剪两张卡
- will have to cut two cards. - [door slams open]
[all gasp]
我叫Rebecca BIoomwood 我是购物狂
I'm Rebecca Bloomwood and I'm a shopaholic.
嗨 Rebecca
[all] Hi, Rebecca.
我在全国电视节目上自毁了前程
I destroyed my career on national television.
我欺骗了深爱的男人  伤害了最好的朋友
I lied to the man I love. I hurt my best friend.
我凭空捏造出一个跟踪狂  我根本不会说芬兰语
I invented a stalker, and I don't even speak Finnish.
但我决心改过 我需要你们的帮助
But I have a plan, and I need your help.
谁会支持我?
Who's with me?
[? Jessie James: Blue Jeans]
感谢上帝
[muted]
"绿围巾女孩 甩卖/拍卖"
不会吧 世纪甩卖
Shut up. Sale of the century.
转发给所有员工 "发送"
Forward to all employees. Send.
Luke 不好意思哦  今天午饭时间能不能长点?
[computer beeps]
Oh, uh, Luke, sorry. Um, may I take a long lunch?
当然 你要干嘛?
Sure. What are you doing?
我有个约会
Oh! Oh, uh, I have an appointment.
- 和谁? - 一个人
- With whom? - A person.
Um...
"绿围巾女孩 甩卖/拍卖"
我猜 她不得不清仓
Uh, I suppose she has to, uh, clear the decks.
腾出空间放置Alette的免费服饰
You know, make room for all those free clothes from Alette.
去吧 HayIey
Go, Hayley.
我能...?
- May I...? - [clears throat]
- 包包! - 就绪!
- Bags! - Ready!
- 配饰! - 就绪!
- Accessories! - Ready!
- 鞋子! - 就绪!
- Shoes! - Ready.
- 女帽 - 你说什么?
- Millinery. - What you call me?
- 帽子 - 哦!
- Hats. - Oh!
希望会有折价鞋子!
I hope they've got shoes!
顾客们已经象热锅上的蚂蚁了
They're gettin' antsy out there.
就等你一声令下 BIoomwood小姐
Ready when you are, Ms. Bloomwood.
开门 老爸!
Open the doors, Dad!
- [? Jordyn Taylor: Accessory] - [all gasping]
[indistinct shouting]
每个人都会有好多哦
There's plenty for everyone.
只要选择...
Just, take your...
瞧瞧这靓丽的颜色
You'll note the delicious color,
时髦的衣领 经典的扣子
the smart collar and these classic buttons.
一口价 30美元
Thirty dollars is my final offer.
我给你30元 你赶紧走吧
I'll give you $30 to get away from my table.
你母亲呢? 她喜欢什么?
What about your mother? What would she like?
严肃的
Sobriety.
- 我觉得... - 这可是幸运罩衫
- I think it's... - It's a lucky top.
这是Prada正品鞋 女士们
These are real Prada shoes, ladies.
正好配这粉色的围巾
They go with the same pink as this scarf.
还有这个包包 这副手套
And the handbag. Oh. And the gloves.
不卖了 不卖了
OK, you know what, not for sale. Not for sale.
- Ptaszinski小姐! - 好吧
- Ms. Ptaszinski! - I'm OK.
现在拍卖...
And now...
[all gasp]
绿色围巾
The green scarf!
标志商品
An icon.
柔软 手感好 象征着金钱的颜色
Supple, sensual, the color of money.
Rebecca品味一流
Rebecca always had such fabulous taste.
难怪她能去Alette杂志工作
No wonder she wound up at Alette magazine.
Becky可没去Alette杂志
Oh, Becky didn't end up at Alette magazine.
她拒绝了那个"机费" (模仿Alette Naylor口音 "机会")
She turned that "hoppertunity" down.
- 什么? 为啥? - 我是Jane BIoomwood 你好
- What? Why? - Yes, Jane Bloomwood, hi.
你好
Oh, hi.
谁会成为下一个绿围巾女孩?
Now who will be the next Girl in the Green Scarf?
- 50元! - 其他报价?
- Fifty dollars! - Anyone else?
- 70 - 有人出价70!
- Seventy. - [Korch] I have 70!
- 90元 - 这位出价90!
- Ninety dollars. - [Korch] Ninety dollars right here!
- 失陪 - 好
- Excuse me. - Sure.
我有位电话投标人 120元
I have a bidder on the phone. One hundred and twenty dollars.
120元买下这条著名美丽高雅的...
One-twenty for the beautiful, famous, elegant...
- 150! - 别卖
- [woman] One-fifty! - Don't sell it.
你已经卖了这么多
You've sold so much already.
- 200元 - 250元
- Two hundred dollars. - Two hundred and fifty dollars.
[all gasp]
250! 有人报价250 你的对手出价250
Two-fifty! I have 250. The bid is against you at 250.
- 怎么样? - 300!
- Well? - Three hundred dollars!
告诉你电话里的朋友 出啥价我都奉陪
You can tell your friend on the phone, I'll match anything they bid.
搞得象个刺客
She's like an assassin.
300元第一次
Three hundred dollars. Going once.
- 第二次 - 我的投标人退出
- Going twice. - My bidder withdraws.
300元成交 这位粉色衣裙的小姐
Sold for 300 to the lady in pink.
等等!
- [Rebecca] Wait! - [all gasping]
呃...
Uh...
- 别和黄色搭配 - 绝不会的
- Don't wear it with yellow. - Never.
- 它会给你带来爱情 - 谢谢
- It could bring you love. - Thank you.
[cheering]
一二三四 又是一千元
One, two, three, four. That's another thousand.
哇
Wow.
16586.72元
$16,586, 72 cents.
你发了 宝贝!
- You are a winner, babe! - [all screaming]
天哪
Oh, my God.
Smeath先生
- [screams] - Mr. Smeath.
见鬼 这是什么? 你在这儿干嘛?
What the hell is this? What are you doing?
你怎么在节目上对我 我怎么对你 Derek
I'm doing exactly what you did to me on that television show, Derek.
把你应得的给你
I'm just giving you what you deserve.
不过是以最麻烦的方式给你
But in the most inconvenient way possible.
这些总共9412元
And that, I think, makes 9,412.
哦 还有25分
Oh. And a quarter.
[indistinct chattering]
让我来
[Rebecca] I've got it. I've got it.
姑娘们 时间到!
[woman] OK. Ladies, it's time!
- 你怎么拿回来的? - 我做了笔交易
- How'd you get it back? - I did a deal.
给她拿束花
Get her some flowers.
- 不好意思 - 去 赶紧去
- Sorry. OK. - Go, go, go, go, go.
- 准备好没 甜心? - Bex!
- Ready, sweetie? - Bex!
来
Come here.
好了
OK.
[? Macy Gray: Don't Forget Me]
婚宴见!
See you at the reception!
你把所有衣服卖了 却独独留了这件?
You sold all your clothes and kept that?
- Suze的婚礼... - 婚礼 我知道
- It's Suze's wedding... - Wedding. I know.
我现在是调查新闻记者 Rebecca
I'm an investigative journalist, Rebecca.
你得相信我能查到
Give me some credit.
你真的全卖了?
You really sold it all?
你可是什么都不剩了
You have nothing left.
我可不这么认为
I mean, I wouldn't put it like that.
[gasps]
我也不这么认为
Neither would I.
电话投标人是你
The bidder on the phone was you.
但你没竞到标!
But you lost!
两个投标人都是我
Both bidders were me.
这可是条至关重要的围巾
It's a desperately important scarf.
姓名:  Rebecca Bloomwood
[Rebecca] Name: Rebecca Bloomwood.
职业:  Luke新杂志的专栏作家
Occupation: I am a columnist for Luke's new magazine.
[? Adrienne Bailon: Big Spender]
衣着: 向Suze借的 因为我是改过自新的购物狂
Dress: Borrowed from Suze as I am a reformed shopaholic.
- 给你 Ryuichi - 哇!
- Here, Ryuichi. - Wow!
不购物时 能有时间做
[Rebecca] It is amazing what you have time to do
很多美妙的事
when you're not shopping.
比如 我真的学了芬兰语
For example, I actually learned Finnish.
这是我的朋友
[speaking Finnish]
她是位有名的妓女
啊...
Ahh... [speaks Finnish]
我不再经营和信用卡的感情
[Rebecca] And instead of a relationship with my credit card,
而是经营和爱人的恋情
I have a relationship with someone who loves me back.
他从不会拒绝我
And never declines me.
你从哪儿学来的这些招式?
Where do you get your moves?
谁知道呢? 就是自然而然想到的
Who knows? It just comes naturally.
没错 谁知道呢 这将是个谜
Oh, you're right. It's a mystery.
（字幕调整lwrest）